[GOAL1]
{Kill the hunter and escape from the ward}
Uccidi il cacciatore e scappa dalla corsia.

[GOAL2]
{Gain access to the Greenhouse section}
Entra nella serra.

[GOAL3]
{Destroy the bricked up doorway to gain access to the tower}
Distruggi la porta di mattoni e guadagna l'accesso alla torre.

[GOAL4]
{Bring proof of the dress-wearing hunter's death to the Guard Room}
Porta la prova dell'uccisione del cacciatore alla sala di guardia.

[GOAL4B]
{Kill the monkey and bring his body to the Guard Room}
Uccidi la scimmia e porta il suo corpo nella sala di guardia.

[CDOOR1]
{He's gonna get away with my damned shoes! Close the door!}
Sta scappando con le mie dannate scarpe! Chiudete la porta!

[CDOOR2]
{Stay boy, stay boy. Close that gate!}
Aspetta, ragazzo, aspetta un momento... Chiudete quella porta!

[CDOOR3]
{Close the gate and stop that wriggly witchetty man!}
Chiudi la porta e ferma quel derelitto ambulante!

[CDOOR4]
{Wuuurrgghh!! Close door! Close door!}
Wuuurrgghh!!! Chiudete la porta! Chiudete la porta!

[CDOOR5]
{Fug see liddle man! Close door! Close door!}
Fug vede un biggolo uomo! Ghiudi la borda! Ghiudi la borda!

[CDOOR6]
{Da door - shud id! Shud id!}
La borda - ghiudila! Ghiudila!

[CDOOR7]
{Don't let that philandering scumball out of here! Close the gate!}
Quella sottospecie di invertebrato non deve uscire vivo di qui! Chiudete la porta!

[CDOOR8]
{Oh no, you're not leaving this house to see her! Girls, lock that door!}
Oh no, scordati pure il tuo appuntamento galante. Ragazze, chiudete la porta!

[CDOOR9]
{Oh you worthless, stupid, drunk! Lock that door!}
Stupido insignificante ubriacone! Chiudete quella porta!

[POWER1]
{Time to play? Time to play! Fug coming!}
È ora di giocare? Giochiamo, allora! Fug sta arrivando!

[POWER2]
{Oohh. Time for Fug to play doctor!}
Oohh. È ora che Fug giochi al dottore!

[LEVER1]
{Doctor Fug make it all better, aaalll better...}
Il dottor Fug ti fa sentire meglio, moooolto meglio...

[LEVER2]
{Don't worry, Fug stob da pain. Fug stob da paaiin.}
Non breoccubarti, Fug verma il dolore. Fug verma il dolooore.

[NOWAY1]
{Who dat? Fug not playing this game...}
Ghi è guello? Fug non gioga a guesdo giogo...

[NOWAY2]
{Huh? Fug not stoopid!}
Uh? Fug non è sdubido!

[ODOOR1]
{Big bonez! Open the door! Bonez!}
Big bonez! Apri la porta! Bonez!

[ODOOR2]
{I can't see Mr. Witchetty! Open the door!}
Non riesco a vedere Mr. Witchetty! Aprite la porta!

[ODOOR3]
{Where's nasty wriggly Mr. Witchetty? Open the door!}
Dov'è quel disgustoso Mr. Witchetty? Aprite la porta!

[ODOOR4]
{He hide from Fug! Open door!}
Si sta nascondendo da Fug! Aprite la porta!

[ODOOR5]
{Open door so Fug can go and see!}
Aprite la porta, così Fug può andare a vedere!

[ODOOR6]
{Fug can't see funny man - Open door! Open door!}
Fug non riesce a vedere quell'uomo. Aprite la porta! Aprite la porta!

[ODOOR7]
{He's sloped off to see that whore again! Open the door, kids!}
È andato ancora da quella puttana! Aprite la porta, bambini!

[ODOOR8]
{Barry? Barry! Where is that shit? Open the door!}
Barry? Barry! Dov'è quel merdoso? Aprite la porta!

[ODOOR9]
{Barry? Barry! Where is that shit? Open the door!}
Barry? Barry! Dov'è quel merdoso? Aprite la porta!

[QUIET1]
{Shut Up!}
Taci!

[QUIET2]
{Argh! Shut up!}
Argh! Chiudi il becco!

[MTH1A1]
{The lunatics have taken over the asylum, Cash!}
Il manicomio è nelle mani dei pazzi, Cash!

[MTH1A2]
{The only way to reason with these gibbering idiots is with a stick and a gun!}
L'unico modo di ragionare con quegli idioti è con un bastone e una pistola.

[MTH1A3]
{I want you to kill the hunter patrolling the tower walkway and bring his body to the Guard Room.}
Voglio che tu uccida il cacciatore di vedetta alla torre e porti il suo corpo nella sala di guardia.

[MTH2A1]
{There's a good boy. Now drop all your weapons and move on.}
Ecco un bravo ragazzo. Ora getta le tue armi e vieni avanti.

[MTH3A1]
{For bringing his head, I'll leave a gift for you in the next location.}
In cambio della sua testa, ti lascerò un regalino nel prossimo set.

[MTH4A1]
{There are some more of these paranoid crazies guarding the door to the greenhouses.}
Ce ne sono altri di questi pazzi paranoici a guardia della porta della serra.

[MTH4A2]
{They see you and I guarantee they'll lock that door!}
Se ti vedono, ti assicuro che chiuderanno a chiave quella porta.

[MTH4A3]
{When they feel safe they'll probably unlock the door again. They like their routine.}
Se si sentono al sicuro, forse sbloccheranno di nuovo la porta. Sono così abitudinari.

[MTH5A1]
{There's a hunter in the next room, through the mesh door.}
C'è un cacciatore nella stanza vicina, oltre l'inferriata.

[MTH5A2]
{Hack him up and I'll buzz open the next set of doors for you!}
Fallo a pezzi e ti aprirò la prossima serie di porte!

[MTH6A1]
{That's the ticket! I've opened the doors, run along, now!}
Così va bene! Ho aperto le porte, ora vai avanti!

[MTH7A1]
{Some of these nut jobs have bricked themselves into the tower!}
Alcuni di questi pazzi si sono barricati nella torre!

[MTH7A2]
{You'll have to find a way to blast your way in!}
Devi trovare un modo per farti strada!

[MTH8A1]
{Another switch! Go on, throw it and see what happens, go on you can trust me...}
Un altro interruttore! Forza, azionalo e vedi cosa succede. Avanti, puoi fidarti di me...

[MTH9A1]
{There, that wasn't anything to worry about, was it?}
Visto, non c'era nulla di cui preoccuparsi, o sbaglio?

[MPG1]
{...the Senator also visited the Darkwoods Penitentiary}
...il Senatore ha anche visitato il penitenziario di Darkwoods,

[MPG2]
{which hosts more than a thousand inmates from all over the country...}
che ospita più di mille reclusi provenienti da tutto il paese...

[MPG3]
{The prison's modern facilities include spacious cells for the inmates}
Le moderne attrezzature della prigione includono celle spaziose per i carcerati

[MPG4]
{...the exceptionally well staffed hospital is equipped for emergencies as well as routine health checks...}
...l'ospedale, molto ben organizzato, è equipaggiato per le emergenze così come per le normali visite di controllo...

[MPG5]
{...adjacent to ROW 1, the electric chair room is where death sentences are carried out...}
...vicino al GIRONE 1, la sala della sedia elettrica è dove vengono eseguite le condanne a morte.

[MPG6]
{Right here...Drop him!}
Ci siamo...lasciatelo!

[DIR_1]
DIRECTOR: Eliminate this hunter and I will open the door for you, make it nice and messy.

[DIR_2]
DIRECTOR: Excellent, I have now unlocked the doors at the far end of the ward.

[DIR_3]
DIRECTOR: Cash I want you to kill this hunter in the dress and bring evidence of his death to the Guard Room.

[DIR_4]
DIRECTOR: Cash, you will need to find a way of destroying the bricked up door to get inside the tower.

[DIR_5]
DIRECTOR: Well done Cash,now on to the next area.

[DIR_6]
DIRECTOR: Cash for bringing his head here I will leave a gift in the next level.

[DIR_7]
DIRECTOR: Cash you will need to past these guards to enter the Greenhouses, if you are spotted they will lock the door.

[DIR_8]
DIRECTOR: When spotted use the shadows to hide. When they can't find you, they will unlock the door.

[DIR_9]
DIRECTOR: Cash, kill the monkey and bring his body to the guard room.

[DIR_10]
DIRECTOR: Cash for bringing his head here I will leave a gift in the next level, but I need you to bring his body.

[DIR_11]
DIRECTOR: Cash, I want you to drop all your weapons and put on the monkey outfit.

[DRCL1]
HUNTER: I see him, I see him, Close the door!

[DROP1]
HUNTER: Shit I can't see him, open the door.

[HUT_1]
WARDHUNTER: Shut the fuck up!, don't make me come through there!

[HUT_2]
WARDHUNTER: Shut the fuck up!

[HUT_3]
{WARDHUNTER: Damn machine! why do I have to turn it off, I should get a remote or something.}
} WARDHUNTER: Damn machine! why do I have to turn it off, I should get a remote or something.

[PAIN]
GUY IN CHAIR: ARRGGG THE PAIN!!!!

[HUT_4]
WARDHUNTER: Shut up I am not playing this game...

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!