[GOAL1]
Kill Piggsy and find a way to reach Starkweather

[GOAL2]
Take care of the Cerberus guards to enter Starkweather's room

[GOAL3]
Kill Starkweather

[GOD]
The chainsaw makes noise when its engine is running. Turn it OFF with the Action2 button.

[SICK1]
Hurthuuurrrrttt!

[SICK2]
No more. Noo moooorre!!

[SICK3]
Going home, hoooooome!

[AWAY1]
Go! Away! Go!

[AWAY2]
Not playing! Not funny!

[AWAY3]
Stop! Not fair! Stop!

[ANGRY1]
Piggsy angry! Aarrgghhnngry!

[ANGRY2]
Rraarggh! Piggsy gonna suck your guts!

[ANGRY3]
This Piggsy's home! Raaarrghh!!!

[HOME1]
Piggsy forget why here...

[HOME2]
Piggsy bored. Go home to bed and sleep...

[HOME3]
Piggsy not play no more. Piggsy go hoome...

[LIFT1]
Starkweather said no unexpected visitors.

[STORM1]
Fuck this, I'm going in!!!!

[STORM2]
I'm coming in there to fuck you up!!!

[STORM3]
Who dares, wins - rraagghh!!!

[DIR]
Send him to hell! Go on!

[MPG9]
Pigsy ANGRY! Unh! Pigsy Angry!

[MPG10]
Ahhh! Yeah! Pigsy Angry!

[MPG1]
Acclaimed movie maker Lionel Starkweather has been found dead today

[MPG2]
along with several of his bodyguards, at his estate at the Wapona Hills residential district.

[MPG3]
In what investigators are calling a bloody vendetta,

[MPG4]
An unknown assailant infiltrated the compound, killing Starkweather,

[MPG5]
but more interestingly, leading police to the site of a snuff film ring being run from the estate's confines.

[MPG6]
Linked to this ring is Carcer City's own police chief Gary Schaffer,

[MPG7]
whose lawyer stated that he intends to plead not guilty.

[MPG8]
Hello Kiddies...

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!