[GOAL1]
Kill the hunter and escape from the ward

[GOAL2]
Gain access to the Greenhouse section

[GOAL3]
Destroy the bricked up doorway to gain access to the tower

[GOAL4]
Bring proof of the dress-wearing hunter's death to the Guard Room

[GOAL4B]
Kill the monkey and bring his body to the Guard Room

[CDOOR1]
He's gonna get away with my damned shoes! Close the door!

[CDOOR2]
Stay boy, stay boy. Close that gate!

[CDOOR3]
Close the gate and stop that wriggly witchetty man!

[CDOOR4]
Wuuurrgghh!! Close door! Close door!

[CDOOR5]
Fug see liddle man! Close door! Close door!

[CDOOR6]
Da door - shud id! Shud id!

[CDOOR7]
Don't let that philandering scumball out of here! Close the gate!

[CDOOR8]
Oh no, you're not leaving this house to see her! Girls, lock that door!

[CDOOR9]
Oh you worthless, stupid, drunk! Lock that door!

[POWER1]
Time to play? Time to play! Fug coming!

[POWER2]
Oohh. Time for Fug to play doctor!

[LEVER1]
Doctor Fug make it all better, aaalll better...

[LEVER2]
Don't worry, Fug stob da pain. Fug stob da paaiin.

[NOWAY1]
Who dat? Fug not playing this game...

[NOWAY2]
Huh? Fug not stoopid!

[ODOOR1]
Big bonez! Open the door! Bonez!

[ODOOR2]
I can't see Mr. Witchetty! Open the door!

[ODOOR3]
Where's nasty wriggly Mr. Witchetty? Open the door!

[ODOOR4]
He hide from Fug! Open door!

[ODOOR5]
Open door so Fug can go and see!

[ODOOR6]
Fug can't see funny man - Open door! Open door!

[ODOOR7]
He's sloped off to see that whore again! Open the door, kids!

[ODOOR8]
Barry? Barry! Where is that shit? Open the door!

[ODOOR9]
Barry? Barry! Where is that shit? Open the door!

[QUIET1]
Shut Up!

[QUIET2]
Argh! Shut up!

[MTH1A1]
The lunatics have taken over the asylum, Cash!

[MTH1A2]
The only way to reason with these gibbering idiots is with a stick and a gun!

[MTH1A3]
I want you to kill the hunter patrolling the tower walkway and bring his body to the Guard Room.

[MTH2A1]
There's a good boy. Now drop all your weapons and move on.

[MTH3A1]
For bringing his head, I'll leave a gift for you in the next location.

[MTH4A1]
There are some more of these paranoid crazies guarding the door to the greenhouses.

[MTH4A2]
They see you and I guarantee they'll lock that door!

[MTH4A3]
When they feel safe they'll probably unlock the door again. They like their routine.

[MTH5A1]
There's a hunter in the next room, through the mesh door.

[MTH5A2]
Hack him up and I'll buzz open the next set of doors for you!

[MTH6A1]
That's the ticket! I've opened the doors, run along, now!

[MTH7A1]
Some of these nut jobs have bricked themselves into the tower!

[MTH7A2]
You'll have to find a way to blast your way in!

[MTH8A1]
Another switch! Go on, throw it and see what happens, go on you can trust me...

[MTH9A1]
There, that wasn't anything to worry about, was it?

[MPG1]
...the Senator also visited the Darkwoods Penitentiary

[MPG2]
which hosts more than a thousand inmates from all over the country...

[MPG3]
The prison's modern facilities include spacious cells for the inmates

[MPG4]
...the exceptionally well staffed hospital is equipped for emergencies as well as routine health checks...

[MPG5]
...adjacent to ROW 1, the electric chair room is where death sentences are carried out...

[MPG6]
Right here...Drop him!

[DIR_1]
DIRECTOR: Eliminate this hunter and I will open the door for you, make it nice and messy.

[DIR_2]
DIRECTOR: Excellent, I have now unlocked the doors at the far end of the ward.

[DIR_3]
DIRECTOR: Cash I want you to kill this hunter in the dress and bring evidence of his death to the Guard Room.

[DIR_4]
DIRECTOR: Cash, you will need to find a way of destroying the bricked up door to get inside the tower.

[DIR_5]
DIRECTOR: Well done Cash,now on to the next area.

[DIR_6]
DIRECTOR: Cash for bringing his head here I will leave a gift in the next level.

[DIR_7]
DIRECTOR: Cash you will need to past these guards to enter the Greenhouses, if you are spotted they will lock the door.

[DIR_8]
DIRECTOR: When spotted use the shadows to hide. When they can't find you, they will unlock the door.

[DIR_9]
DIRECTOR: Cash, kill the monkey and bring his body to the guard room.

[DIR_10]
DIRECTOR: Cash for bringing his head here I will leave a gift in the next level, but I need you to bring his body.

[DIR_11]
DIRECTOR: Cash, I want you to drop all your weapons and put on the monkey outfit.

[DRCL1]
HUNTER: I see him, I see him, Close the door!

[DROP1]
HUNTER: Shit I can't see him, open the door.

[HUT_1]
WARDHUNTER: Shut the fuck up!, don't make me come through there!

[HUT_2]
WARDHUNTER: Shut the fuck up!

[HUT_3]
WARDHUNTER: Damn machine! why do I have to turn it off, I should get a remote or something.

[PAIN]
GUY IN CHAIR: ARRGGG THE PAIN!!!!

[HUT_4]
WARDHUNTER: Shut up I am not playing this game...

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!