[GOAL1]
{Kill the hunter and escape from the ward}
Mata al cazador y escapa de la sala

[GOAL2]
{Gain access to the Greenhouse section}
Consigue acceso a la sección del invernadero

[GOAL3]
{Destroy the bricked up doorway to gain access to the tower}
Derriba la puerta tapiada para poder acceder a la torre

[GOAL4]
{Bring proof of the dress-wearing hunter's death to the Guard Room}
Lleva pruebas de la muerte del cazador a la sala de guardia

[GOAL4B]
{Kill the monkey and bring his body to the Guard Room}
Mata al pringado y lleva su cuerpo a la sala de guardia

[CDOOR1]
{He's gonna get away with my damned shoes! Close the door!}
¡Se va a ir con mis jodidos zapatos! ¡Cerrad la puerta!

[CDOOR2]
{Stay boy, stay boy. Close that gate!}
Quieto, quieto. ¡Cerrad la puerta!

[CDOOR3]
{Close the gate and stop that wriggly witchetty man!}
¡Cerrad la puerta y detened a ese rastrero sacamantecas!

[CDOOR4]
{Wuuurrgghh!! Close door! Close door!}
¡Aarrrrrghhh! ¡Cerrad la puerta! ¡Cerrad la puerta!

[CDOOR5]
{Fug see liddle man! Close door! Close door!}
¡Fug ve a hombre pequeñito! ¡Cerrad la puerta! ¡Cerrad la puerta!

[CDOOR6]
{Da door - shud id! Shud id!}
La puerta. Cerradla, cerradla.

[CDOOR7]
{Don't let that philandering scumball out of here! Close the gate!}
¡No dejéis que esa basura ligona salga de aquí! ¡Cerrad la puerta!

[CDOOR8]
{Oh no, you're not leaving this house to see her! Girls, lock that door!}
Oh, no. ¡No vas a salir de esta casa para verla! Chicas, ¡cerrad la puerta!

[CDOOR9]
{Oh you worthless, stupid, drunk! Lock that door!}
¡Oh, inútil, estúpido y borracho holgazán! ¡Cerrad la puerta!

[POWER1]
{Time to play? Time to play! Fug coming!}
¿Quieres jugar? ¡Juguemos! ¡Allá va Fug!

[POWER2]
{Oohh. Time for Fug to play doctor!}
Oohh. ¡Toca que Fug juegue a los doctores!

[LEVER1]
{Doctor Fug make it all better, aaalll better...}
Doctor Fug lo hace todo mejor, tooodooo mejor...

[LEVER2]
{Don't worry, Fug stob da pain. Fug stob da paaiin.}
No te preocupes, Fug parará el dolor. Fug parará el dolooor

[NOWAY1]
{Who dat? Fug not playing this game...}
¿Qué? Fug no jugará a este juego...

[NOWAY2]
{Huh? Fug not stoopid!}
¿Eh? ¡Fug no es estúuupido!

[ODOOR1]
{Big bonez! Open the door! Bonez!}
¡Huesazos! ¡Abrid la puerta! ¡Huesos!

[ODOOR2]
{I can't see Mr. Witchetty! Open the door!}
¡Puedo ver al sacamantecas! ¡Abrid la puerta!

[ODOOR3]
{Where's nasty wriggly Mr. Witchetty? Open the door!}
¿Dónde está asqueroso y desagradable sacamantecas? ¡Abrid la puerta!

[ODOOR4]
{He hide from Fug! Open door!}
¡Se esconde de Fug! ¡Abrid la puerta!

[ODOOR5]
{Open door so Fug can go and see!}
¡Abrid la puerta para que Fug pueda entrar y ver!

[ODOOR6]
{Fug can't see funny man - Open door! Open door!}
Fug no puede ver al listillo. ¡Abrid la puerta! ¡Abrid la puerta!

[ODOOR7]
{He's sloped off to see that whore again! Open the door, kids!}
¡Se ha escabullido otra vez a ver a esa fulana! ¡Niños, abrid la puerta!

[ODOOR8]
{Barry? Barry! Where is that shit? Open the door!}
¿Barry? ¡Barry! ¿Dónde está esa mierda? ¡Abrid la puerta!

[ODOOR9]
{Barry? Barry! Where is that shit? Open the door!}
¿Barry? ¡Barry! ¿Dónde está esa mierda? ¡Abrid la puerta!

[QUIET1]
{Shut Up!}
¡Cierra la boca!

[QUIET2]
{Argh! Shut up!}
¡Aj! ¡Cállate de una vez!

[MTH1A1]
{The lunatics have taken over the asylum, Cash!}
¡Los locos han tomado el manicomio, Cash!

[MTH1A2]
{The only way to reason with these gibbering idiots is with a stick and a gun!}
¡La única forma de tratar con estos idiotas babeantes es con un palo y un arma!

[MTH1A3]
{I want you to kill the hunter patrolling the tower walkway and bring his body to the Guard Room.}
Quiero que mates al cazador que está patrullando el pasillo de la torre y que lleves su cuerpo a la sala de guardia.

[MTH2A1]
{There's a good boy. Now drop all your weapons and move on.}
Buen chico. Ahora deja todas tus armas y muévete.

[MTH3A1]
{For bringing his head, I'll leave a gift for you in the next location.}
Ya que has traído su cabeza, te dejaré un regalo en la siguiente localización.

[MTH4A1]
{There are some more of these paranoid crazies guarding the door to the greenhouses.}
Hay más de esos zumbados paranoicos vigilando la puerta del invernadero.

[MTH4A2]
{They see you and I guarantee they'll lock that door!}
¡Si te ven, te garantizo que cerrarán la puerta!

[MTH4A3]
{When they feel safe they'll probably unlock the door again. They like their routine.}
Cuando se sientan a salvo, seguramente volverán a abrir la puerta. Les gusta la rutina.

[MTH5A1]
{There's a hunter in the next room, through the mesh door.}
Hay un cazador en la siguiente habitación, al otro lado de la puerta de malla metálica.

[MTH5A2]
{Hack him up and I'll buzz open the next set of doors for you!}
¡Machácale y me encargaré de abrir la siguiente serie de puertas!

[MTH6A1]
{That's the ticket! I've opened the doors, run along, now!}
¡Es lo que hace falta! He abierto las puertas, corre, ¡ya!

[MTH7A1]
{Some of these nut jobs have bricked themselves into the tower!}
¡Algunos de estos idiotas se han encerrado en la torre!

[MTH7A2]
{You'll have to find a way to blast your way in!}
¡Tendrás que encontrar la forma de abrirte camino!

[MTH8A1]
{Another switch! Go on, throw it and see what happens, go on you can trust me...}
¡Otro interruptor! Vamos, actívalo y veamos qué pasa, vamos, puedes confiar en mí...

[MTH9A1]
{There, that wasn't anything to worry about, was it?}
Ya, no había de qué preocuparse, ¿verdad?

[MPG1]
{...the Senator also visited the Darkwoods Penitentiary}
... el senador también ha visitado el centro penitenciario Darkwoods

[MPG2]
{which hosts more than a thousand inmates from all over the country...}
que tiene más de un millar de internos provenientes de todo el país...

[MPG3]
{The prison's modern facilities include spacious cells for the inmates}
Las modernas instalaciones de la prisión incluyen amplias celdas para los internos

[MPG4]
{...the exceptionally well staffed hospital is equipped for emergencies as well as routine health checks...}
... la plantilla magníficamente preparada que trabaja en el hospital está equipada para emergencias, así como para chequeos rutinarios...

[MPG5]
{...adjacent to ROW 1, the electric chair room is where death sentences are carried out...}
... junto a la galería 1, la sala de la silla eléctrica es donde se ejecutan las sentencias de muerte...

[MPG6]
{Right here...Drop him!}
Justo aquí, ¡déjalo!

[DIR_1]
DIRECTOR: Eliminate this hunter and I will open the door for you, make it nice and messy.

[DIR_2]
DIRECTOR: Excellent, I have now unlocked the doors at the far end of the ward.

[DIR_3]
DIRECTOR: Cash I want you to kill this hunter in the dress and bring evidence of his death to the Guard Room.

[DIR_4]
DIRECTOR: Cash, you will need to find a way of destroying the bricked up door to get inside the tower.

[DIR_5]
DIRECTOR: Well done Cash,now on to the next area.

[DIR_6]
DIRECTOR: Cash for bringing his head here I will leave a gift in the next level.

[DIR_7]
DIRECTOR: Cash you will need to past these guards to enter the Greenhouses, if you are spotted they will lock the door.

[DIR_8]
DIRECTOR: When spotted use the shadows to hide. When they can't find you, they will unlock the door.

[DIR_9]
DIRECTOR: Cash, kill the monkey and bring his body to the guard room.

[DIR_10]
DIRECTOR: Cash for bringing his head here I will leave a gift in the next level, but I need you to bring his body.

[DIR_11]
DIRECTOR: Cash, I want you to drop all your weapons and put on the monkey outfit.

[DRCL1]
HUNTER: I see him, I see him, Close the door!

[DROP1]
HUNTER: Shit I can't see him, open the door.

[HUT_1]
WARDHUNTER: Shut the fuck up!, don't make me come through there!

[HUT_2]
WARDHUNTER: Shut the fuck up!

[HUT_3]
{WARDHUNTER: Damn machine! why do I have to turn it off, I should get a remote or something.}
} WARDHUNTER: Damn machine! why do I have to turn it off, I should get a remote or something.

[PAIN]
GUY IN CHAIR: ARRGGG THE PAIN!!!!

[HUT_4]
WARDHUNTER: Shut up I am not playing this game...

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!