[GOAL1]
{Kill the hunter and escape from the ward}
Bute le chasseur et sors du service.

[GOAL2]
{Gain access to the Greenhouse section}
Trouve un moyen d'accéder à la serre.

[GOAL3]
{Destroy the bricked up doorway to gain access to the tower}
Défonce la porte murée pour accéder à la tour.

[GOAL4]
{Bring proof of the dress-wearing hunter's death to the Guard Room}
Apporte la preuve de la mort du chasseur travelo à la salle de garde.

[GOAL4B]
{Kill the monkey and bring his body to the Guard Room}
Bute le macaque et amène son corps à la salle de garde.

[CDOOR1]
{He's gonna get away with my damned shoes! Close the door!}
Il se casse avec mes putains de pompes ! Fermez la porte !

[CDOOR2]
{Stay boy, stay boy. Close that gate!}
Au pied, bouge pas ! Fermez cette porte !

[CDOOR3]
{Close the gate and stop that wriggly witchetty man!}
Bouclez cette porte et arrêtez ce malade !

[CDOOR4]
{Wuuurrgghh!! Close door! Close door!}
Aaaaaaargh ! Fermez la porte ! Vite !

[CDOOR5]
{Fug see liddle man! Close door! Close door!}
Fug a vu p'tit gars ! Fermez porte ! Fermez porte !

[CDOOR6]
{Da door - shud id! Shud id!}
La lourde ! Bouclez-la, bouclez-la !

[CDOOR7]
{Don't let that philandering scumball out of here! Close the gate!}
Laissez pas ce taré rentrer ici ! Bouclez cette putain de porte !

[CDOOR8]
{Oh no, you're not leaving this house to see her! Girls, lock that door!}
Oh non, tu vas pas te barrer la voir, ça non ! Les filles, fermez cette porte !

[CDOOR9]
{Oh you worthless, stupid, drunk! Lock that door!}
T'es qu'un poivrot complètement allumé ! Fermez cette porte !

[POWER1]
{Time to play? Time to play! Fug coming!}
On joue ? Hein, on joue ? Fug arrive !

[POWER2]
{Oohh. Time for Fug to play doctor!}
Oooh. C'est l'heure du docteur Fug !

[LEVER1]
{Doctor Fug make it all better, aaalll better...}
Docteur Fug va tout arranger, tout ira bieeeen mieux...

[LEVER2]
{Don't worry, Fug stob da pain. Fug stob da paaiin.}
Pas de soucis, avec Fug, pas de douleur. Pas de douuuuleeeur...

[NOWAY1]
{Who dat? Fug not playing this game...}
Qui t'es, toi ? Fug joue plus...

[NOWAY2]
{Huh? Fug not stoopid!}
Hein ? Fug pas con !

[ODOOR1]
{Big bonez! Open the door! Bonez!}
Braquemart ! Ouvre la lourde ! Braquemart !

[ODOOR2]
{I can't see Mr. Witchetty! Open the door!}
Je vois plus la méchante larve ! Ouvrez la porte !

[ODOOR3]
{Where's nasty wriggly Mr. Witchetty? Open the door!}
Où est la méchante larve ? Ouvrez la porte !

[ODOOR4]
{He hide from Fug! Open door!}
Il se cache de Fug ! Ouvrez porte !

[ODOOR5]
{Open door so Fug can go and see!}
Ouvrez porte, Fug veut aller voir !

[ODOOR6]
{Fug can't see funny man - Open door! Open door!}
Fug pas vu mec zarbi ! Ouvrez porte ! Ouvrez porte !

[ODOOR7]
{He's sloped off to see that whore again! Open the door, kids!}
Il s'est barré pour voir cette pute ! Ouvrez la porte, les enfants !

[ODOOR8]
{Barry? Barry! Where is that shit? Open the door!}
Barry ? Barry ? Où est ce connard ? Ouvrez la porte !

[ODOOR9]
{Barry? Barry! Where is that shit? Open the door!}
Barry ? Barry ? Où est ce petit connard ? Ouvrez la porte !

[QUIET1]
{Shut Up!}
Ta gueule !

[QUIET2]
{Argh! Shut up!}
Argh ! Ta gueule !

[MTH1A1]
{The lunatics have taken over the asylum, Cash!}
Cash ! Les malades ont pris le contrôle de l'asile!

[MTH1A2]
{The only way to reason with these gibbering idiots is with a stick and a gun!}
Un seul moyen de les ramener à la raison : une bonne raclée !

[MTH1A3]
{I want you to kill the hunter patrolling the tower walkway and bring his body to the Guard Room.}
Je veux que tu butes le chasseur sur le mirador et que t'amènes son corps à la salle de garde.

[MTH2A1]
{There's a good boy. Now drop all your weapons and move on.}
Brave petit. Maintenant, vire toutes tes armes et continue.

[MTH3A1]
{For bringing his head, I'll leave a gift for you in the next location.}
Pour m'avoir apporté sa tête, t'auras un joli cadeau à ta prochaine destination.

[MTH4A1]
{There are some more of these paranoid crazies guarding the door to the greenhouses.}
Y'a d'autres tarés qui gardent la porte de la serre.

[MTH4A2]
{They see you and I guarantee they'll lock that door!}
S'ils te voient, je te garantis qu'ils boucleront cette porte !

[MTH4A3]
{When they feel safe they'll probably unlock the door again. They like their routine.}
Ils ne la rouvriront que s'ils se sentent en sécurité. Ils aiment bien suivre la procédure.

[MTH5A1]
{There's a hunter in the next room, through the mesh door.}
Y'a un chasseur dans la pièce suivante, derrière la porte grillagée.

[MTH5A2]
{Hack him up and I'll buzz open the next set of doors for you!}
Règle-lui son compte et je t'ouvrirai les autres portes !

[MTH6A1]
{That's the ticket! I've opened the doors, run along, now!}
Voilà ton ticket d'entrée ! Les portes sont ouvertes, allez ! Fonce !

[MTH7A1]
{Some of these nut jobs have bricked themselves into the tower!}
Certains de ces allumés se sont emmurés dans la tour !

[MTH7A2]
{You'll have to find a way to blast your way in!}
Va falloir que tu trouves un moyen d'entrer !

[MTH8A1]
{Another switch! Go on, throw it and see what happens, go on you can trust me...}
Un autre interrupteur ! Essaie-le, qu'on voie ce qui se passe. Allez, fais-moi confiance...

[MTH9A1]
{There, that wasn't anything to worry about, was it?}
Tu vois, y'avait pas de quoi s'inquiéter, hein ?

[MPG1]
{...the Senator also visited the Darkwoods Penitentiary}
... Le sénateur a également visité le pénitencier de Darkwoods

[MPG2]
{which hosts more than a thousand inmates from all over the country...}
qui accueille plus d'un millier de détenus de tout le pays...

[MPG3]
{The prison's modern facilities include spacious cells for the inmates}
Les installations très modernes de la prison incluent de spacieuses cellules

[MPG4]
{...the exceptionally well staffed hospital is equipped for emergencies as well as routine health checks...}
... l'hôpital, avec son personnel spécialisé, est aussi bien équipé pour les urgences que pour les examens de routine...

[MPG5]
{...adjacent to ROW 1, the electric chair room is where death sentences are carried out...}
... près du couloir 1, la salle de la chaise électrique attend l'exécution des condamnés à mort..

[MPG6]
{Right here...Drop him!}
Là ! Lâche-le !

[DIR_1]
DIRECTOR: Eliminate this hunter and I will open the door for you, make it nice and messy.

[DIR_2]
DIRECTOR: Excellent, I have now unlocked the doors at the far end of the ward.

[DIR_3]
DIRECTOR: Cash I want you to kill this hunter in the dress and bring evidence of his death to the Guard Room.

[DIR_4]
DIRECTOR: Cash, you will need to find a way of destroying the bricked up door to get inside the tower.

[DIR_5]
DIRECTOR: Well done Cash,now on to the next area.

[DIR_6]
DIRECTOR: Cash for bringing his head here I will leave a gift in the next level.

[DIR_7]
DIRECTOR: Cash you will need to past these guards to enter the Greenhouses, if you are spotted they will lock the door.

[DIR_8]
DIRECTOR: When spotted use the shadows to hide. When they can't find you, they will unlock the door.

[DIR_9]
DIRECTOR: Cash, kill the monkey and bring his body to the guard room.

[DIR_10]
DIRECTOR: Cash for bringing his head here I will leave a gift in the next level, but I need you to bring his body.

[DIR_11]
DIRECTOR: Cash, I want you to drop all your weapons and put on the monkey outfit.

[DRCL1]
HUNTER: I see him, I see him, Close the door!

[DROP1]
HUNTER: Shit I can't see him, open the door.

[HUT_1]
WARDHUNTER: Shut the fuck up!, don't make me come through there!

[HUT_2]
WARDHUNTER: Shut the fuck up!

[HUT_3]
WARDHUNTER: Damn machine! why do I have to turn it off, I should get a remote or something.

[PAIN]
GUY IN CHAIR: ARRGGG THE PAIN!!!!

[HUT_4]
WARDHUNTER: Shut up I am not playing this game...

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!