[HELP1]
{You must survive for as long as you can against the three gangs. The gangs will fight each other as well as you. Good Luck!}
Du musst so lange wie möglich gegen die drei Banden durchhalten. Die Banden bekämpfen sich auch untereinander. Viel Glück!

[GOAL1]
{Survive for as long as you can}
Überlebe so lang wie möglich.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!