[HELP1]
{You must survive for as long as you can against the three gangs. The gangs will fight each other as well as you. Good Luck!}
Tu dois survivre aussi longtemps que tu peux face aux trois gangs, qui s'affronteront entre eux, mais qui t'oublieront pas non plus. Bonne chance !

[GOAL1]
{Survive for as long as you can}
Survis aussi longtemps que tu peux !

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!