[HELP1]
{You must survive for as long as you can against the three gangs. The gangs will fight each other as well as you. Good Luck!}
Sopravvivi il più a lungo possibile contro le tre bande. Queste, nel frattempo, si combatteranno fra loro. Buona fortuna!

[GOAL1]
{Survive for as long as you can}
Sopravvivi il più a lungo possibile.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!