[HELP1]
{You must survive for as long as you can against the three gangs. The gangs will fight each other as well as you. Good Luck!}
Tienes que sobrevivir todo lo que puedas contra las tres bandas. Las bandas lucharán entre ellas además de contra ti. ¡Buena suerte!

[GOAL1]
{Survive for as long as you can}
Sobrevive todo lo que puedas.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!