[GOAL0]
{Find the ~green~Hammer~colour~}
Finde den ~green~Hammer~colour~.

[GOAL1P1]
{Perform 1 ~yellow~Violent~colour~ execution with the Hammer}
Begehe 1 ~yellow~brutalen~colour~ Mord mit dem Hammer.

[GOAL1P2]
{Perform 1 ~red~Gruesome~colour~ execution with the Hammer}
Begehe 1 ~red~barbarischen~colour~ Mord mit dem Hammer.

[GOAL1P3]
{Get the Bat from the hunter}
Nimm dem Jäger die Keule ab.

[GOAL2P1]
{Perform 1 ~yellow~Violent~colour~ execution with the Bat}
Begehe 1 ~yellow~brutalen~colour~ Mord mit der Keule.

[GOAL2P2]
{Perform 1 ~red~Gruesome~colour~ execution with the Bat}
Begehe 1 ~red~barbarischen~colour~ Mord mit der Keule.

[GOAL2]
{Make your way to the end of the Cellblock}
Kämpfe dich bis zum Ende des Zellenblocks durch.

[GOAL3]
{Go along the top of the Cellblock and get to the shower block}
Gehe an den oberen Zellenblocks vorbei zu den Duschen.

[GOAL4]
{Kill all the hunters}
Töte alle Jäger.

[GOAL5]
{Go to the shower block}
Gehe zu den Duschen.

[GETHAM]
{Find the Hammer somewhere in the Cellblock.}
Finde den im Zellenblock versteckten Hammer.

[GODHAM]
{Perform a ~yellow~Violent~colour~ and a ~red~Gruesome~colour~ execution with the Hammer.}
Begehe einen ~yellow~brutalen~colour~ und einen ~red~barbarischen~colour~ Mord mit dem Hammer.

[GETBAT]
{Kill this hunter and get his Bat.}
Töte diesen Jäger und hol dir seine Keule.

[GODBAT]
{Perform a ~yellow~Violent~colour~ and a ~red~Gruesome~colour~ execution with the Bat.}
Begehe einen ~yellow~brutalen~colour~- und einen ~red~barbarischen~colour~ Mord mit der Keule.

[USEBAT]
{Use the Bat to perform the executions.}
Benutze die Keule für die Morde.

[FUGIN1]
{Look like it up to Fug, Fuuuuuug!!!}
Das wohl eine Sache für Fug, Fug!

[FUGIN2]
{Fug gonna finish this!}
Fug bringt Sache zu Ende!

[FUGIN3]
{Fug gonna make you sorreeeee!}
Fug es dich bereuen lassen!

[JAL1A1]
{Monkey see, monkey kill! That's your motivation for the next scenes!}
Du sehen, du töten! Das sind deine Regieanweisungen für die nächsten Szenen!

[JAL1A2]
{You're killing to entertain, so take your time and play to the camera!}
Du tötest zur Unterhaltung, also lass dir Zeit und spiel ein bisschen mit der Kamera!

[JAL2A1]
{Jesus, Cash, you're chewing through these guys like you were popping bubble wrap.}
Mein Gott, Cash, du verarbeitest diese Kerle ja schneller zu Hackfleisch als ein Fleischwolf.

[JAL2A2]
{Head over to the end of the cell block - I've got a surprise for you.}
Geh ans Ende des Zellenblocks - Ich habe eine Überraschung für dich.

[JAL3A1]
{Get your funky ass along the walkway and head into the shower block.}
Beweg deinen verschissenen Hintern über den Gang zu den Duschen.

[JAL4A1]
{Kill 'em all, Cash, kill 'em all! Ha ha ha!}
Töte sie alle, Cash, töte sie alle! Ha ha ha!

[JAL5A1]
{Here's your reward for being such a good head collector!}
Hier ist die Belohnung für einen ganz hervorragenden Kopfjäger!

[JAL6A1]
{Ok, Cash. You've performed brilliantly.}
Gut, Cash. Du warst einfach brillant.

[JAL6A2]
{Don't worry, I've got plenty more Wonderland fun lined up for you}
Keine Angst, auf dich wartet noch jede Menge wundervoller Spaß!

[JAL6A3]
{(laughter)}
Ha ha ha ...

[CEL1A1]
Ah welcome, the idea of this little game is for you to execute all the hunters looking for you, thats if they dont find you first

[CEL2A1]
Well done, you do still have some surprises left in you, make your way to the end of the cellblock I have a few more surprises for you.

[CEL3A1]
If you wanna get out of here your gonna have to lose that guy and then make your way along the top of the cells to the shower block

[CEL4A1]
If you wanna get in here your gonna have to lose the attencion of those hunters

[BONUS]
Here is your reward for being such a good head collector

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!