[GOAL0]
{Find the ~green~Hammer~colour~}
Trova il ~green~martello~colour~.

[GOAL1P1]
{Perform 1 ~yellow~Violent~colour~ execution with the Hammer}
Compi una ~yellow~violenta~colour~ esecuzione con il martello.

[GOAL1P2]
{Perform 1 ~red~Gruesome~colour~ execution with the Hammer}
Compi una ~red~sanguinosa~colour~ esecuzione con il martello.

[GOAL1P3]
{Get the Bat from the hunter}
Prendi la mazza del cacciatore.

[GOAL2P1]
{Perform 1 ~yellow~Violent~colour~ execution with the Bat}
Compi una ~yellow~violenta~colour~ esecuzione con la mazza.

[GOAL2P2]
{Perform 1 ~red~Gruesome~colour~ execution with the Bat}
Compi una ~red~sanguinosa~colour~ esecuzione con la mazza.

[GOAL2]
{Make your way to the end of the Cellblock}
Arriva alla fine dell'ala di detenzione.

[GOAL3]
{Go along the top of the Cellblock and get to the shower block}
Supera l'ala di detenzione e raggiungi le docce.

[GOAL4]
{Kill all the hunters}
Uccidi tutti i cacciatori.

[GOAL5]
{Go to the shower block}
Vai alle docce.

[GETHAM]
{Find the Hammer somewhere in the Cellblock.}
Trova il martello nell'ala di detenzione.

[GODHAM]
{Perform a ~yellow~Violent~colour~ and a ~red~Gruesome~colour~ execution with the Hammer.}
Compi una ~yellow~violenta~colour~ e una ~red~sanguinosa~colour~ esecuzione con il martello.

[GETBAT]
{Kill this hunter and get his Bat.}
Uccidi il cacciatore e prendi la sua mazza.

[GODBAT]
{Perform a ~yellow~Violent~colour~ and a ~red~Gruesome~colour~ execution with the Bat.}
Compi una ~yellow~violenta~colour~ e una ~red~sanguinosa~colour~ esecuzione con la mazza.

[USEBAT]
{Use the Bat to perform the executions.}
Usa la mazza per compiere l'esecuzione.

[FUGIN1]
{Look like it up to Fug, Fuuuuuug!!!}
Sembra che ora togghi a Fug, Fuuuuuug!!!

[FUGIN2]
{Fug gonna finish this!}
Fug fa bulizia!

[FUGIN3]
{Fug gonna make you sorreeeee!}
Fug di varà rimbiangere di essere nado!

[JAL1A1]
{Monkey see, monkey kill! That's your motivation for the next scenes!}
Spropositata violenza selvaggia! Questo sarà il tuo motto per le prossime scene.

[JAL1A2]
{You're killing to entertain, so take your time and play to the camera!}
Tu uccidi per intrattenere, quindi calati nella parte e sorridi sempre alla telecamera!

[JAL2A1]
{Jesus, Cash, you're chewing through these guys like you were popping bubble wrap.}
Sei un vero demonio, Cash, stai falcidiando questi poveretti come se fossero marionette.

[JAL2A2]
{Head over to the end of the cell block - I've got a surprise for you.}
Raggiungi la fine dell'ala di detenzione... Ho una sorpresa per te.

[JAL3A1]
{Get your funky ass along the walkway and head into the shower block.}
Muovi il tuo fottuto culo e vai alle docce.

[JAL4A1]
{Kill 'em all, Cash, kill 'em all! Ha ha ha!}
Uccidili tutti, Cash, uccidili tutti! Ah ah ah!

[JAL5A1]
{Here's your reward for being such a good head collector!}
Ecco il tuo compenso per aver collezionato così tante teste!

[JAL6A1]
{Ok, Cash. You've performed brilliantly.}
Ok, Cash, te la sei cavata egregiamente.

[JAL6A2]
{Don't worry, I've got plenty more Wonderland fun lined up for you}
Non preoccuparti, ho molti Paesi delle Meraviglie pronti per te.

[JAL6A3]
{(laughter)}
(risata)

[CEL1A1]
Ah welcome, the idea of this little game is for you to execute all the hunters looking for you, thats if they dont find you first

[CEL2A1]
Well done, you do still have some surprises left in you, make your way to the end of the cellblock I have a few more surprises for you.

[CEL3A1]
If you wanna get out of here your gonna have to lose that guy and then make your way along the top of the cells to the shower block

[CEL4A1]
If you wanna get in here your gonna have to lose the attencion of those hunters

[BONUS]
Here is your reward for being such a good head collector

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!