[GOAL0]
Find the ~green~Hammer~colour~

[GOAL1P1]
Perform 1 ~yellow~Violent~colour~ execution with the Hammer

[GOAL1P2]
Perform 1 ~red~Gruesome~colour~ execution with the Hammer

[GOAL1P3]
Get the Bat from the hunter

[GOAL2P1]
Perform 1 ~yellow~Violent~colour~ execution with the Bat

[GOAL2P2]
Perform 1 ~red~Gruesome~colour~ execution with the Bat

[GOAL2]
Make your way to the end of the Cellblock

[GOAL3]
Go along the top of the Cellblock and get to the shower block

[GOAL4]
Kill all the hunters

[GOAL5]
Go to the shower block

[GETHAM]
Find the Hammer somewhere in the Cellblock.

[GODHAM]
Perform a ~yellow~Violent~colour~ and a ~red~Gruesome~colour~ execution with the Hammer.

[GETBAT]
Kill this hunter and get his Bat.

[GODBAT]
Perform a ~yellow~Violent~colour~ and a ~red~Gruesome~colour~ execution with the Bat.

[USEBAT]
Use the Bat to perform the executions.

[FUGIN1]
Look like it up to Fug, Fuuuuuug!!!

[FUGIN2]
Fug gonna finish this!

[FUGIN3]
Fug gonna make you sorreeeee!

[JAL1A1]
Monkey see, monkey kill! That's your motivation for the next scenes!

[JAL1A2]
You're killing to entertain, so take your time and play to the camera!

[JAL2A1]
Jesus, Cash, you're chewing through these guys like you were popping bubble wrap.

[JAL2A2]
Head over to the end of the cell block - I've got a surprise for you.

[JAL3A1]
Get your funky ass along the walkway and head into the shower block.

[JAL4A1]
Kill 'em all, Cash, kill 'em all! Ha ha ha!

[JAL5A1]
Here's your reward for being such a good head collector!

[JAL6A1]
Ok, Cash. You've performed brilliantly.

[JAL6A2]
Don't worry, I've got plenty more Wonderland fun lined up for you

[JAL6A3]
(laughter)

[CEL1A1]
Ah welcome, the idea of this little game is for you to execute all the hunters looking for you, thats if they dont find you first

[CEL2A1]
Well done, you do still have some surprises left in you, make your way to the end of the cellblock I have a few more surprises for you.

[CEL3A1]
If you wanna get out of here your gonna have to lose that guy and then make your way along the top of the cells to the shower block

[CEL4A1]
If you wanna get in here your gonna have to lose the attencion of those hunters

[BONUS]
Here is your reward for being such a good head collector

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!