[GOAL1]
{Get to the street}
Raggiungi la strada.

[GOAL2]
{Find something to break the ~blue~PADLOCK~colour~}
Trova qualcosa per forzare il ~blue~LUCCHETTO~colour~.

[GOAL3]
{Use the CROWBAR to break the ~blue~PADLOCK~colour~}
Usa il PIEDE DI PORCO per forzare il ~blue~LUCCHETTO~colour~.

[GOAL4]
{Win the fight in the cellar}
Vinci il combattimento nella cantina.

[GOAL5]
{Head through the buildings to get to the library}
Attraversa gli edifici per raggiungere la libreria.

[GOAL6]
{Go through the cellar to the exit}
Per uscire, passa per la cantina.

[BLUE]
{One handed weapons like the Bat are ~blue~Blue ~colour~Objects. They are not lost after use but make noise during executions.}
Le armi a una sola mano, come la mazza, sono oggetti di colore ~blue~blu~colour~. Non vengono perse dopo averle usate, ma fanno rumore durante le esecuzioni.

[SWAP]
{You can select individual weapons using the four Inventory Item buttons, or cycle through them with the Inventory button.}
Puoi selezionare un'arma utilizzando i quattro tasti Oggetto Inventario, o alternarle utilizzando il tasto Inventario.

[GRAVE]
{Walking on gravel will make noise that attracts the hunters.}
Muoversi sulla ghiaia farà rumore e attirerà i cacciatori.

[BREAK]
{Special Windows like this one can be smashed. They will create a glass shard for you to collect.}
Finestre speciali come questa possono essere infrante... Produrranno un frammento di vetro che potrai raccogliere.

[LOOK]
{Hold down the First Person button to view your surroundings. You can use this to spot hunters at a distance.}
Tieni premuto il tasto Prima Persona per guardarti intorno. Puoi usare questa funzione per individuare i cacciatori a distanza.

[WBAT]
{Big weapons like this Baseball Bat are ~red~RED ~colour~items. They are stronger, but not as fast as the lighter weapons.}
Le armi pesanti, come la mazza da baseball, sono oggetti di colore ~red~rosso~colour~. Sono più potenti, ma meno veloci delle armi leggere.

[START0]
{You can look behind you by pressing down the Look Back button.}
Puoi guardarti alle spalle premendo il tasto Guarda Dietro.

[START2]
~!~

[START1]
~!~

[SMASH]
{Select the crowbar then press the Use button to break the padlock.}
Seleziona il piede di porco e premi il tasto Usa per rompere il lucchetto.

[GRAB]
{Press the Action and the Action2 buttons together to grapple. Time the attack right and you can chain 3 hits together.}
Premi contemporaneamente i tasti Azione e Azione 2 per una presa. Scegli il momento giusto per attaccare e potrai inanellare tre colpi consecutivi.

[GRAB2]
{To break free from a hunter's grapple press the Action button repeatedly.}
Per liberarti dalla presa di un cacciatore, premi il tasto Azione ripetutamente.

[BAT]
{The bigger weapons are stronger but not as fast as the lighter weapons like the crowbar.}
Le armi pesanti sono più potenti, ma meno veloci delle armi leggere come il piede di porco.

[TRIAN]
{The Crowbar can be used to break padlocks and other locked objects.}
Il piede di porco può essere usato per rompere lucchetti e altri oggetti con serratura.

[RADAR]
{Objectives are shown as a dot on the radar.}
Gli obiettivi sono mostrati come puntini colorati sul radar.

[PISS]
{Hunter : I'm taking a leak, I'll be out in the alley.}
Cacciatore: devo fare una pisciata, la farò nel vicolo.

[PISS1]
{I need a leak. I'll be outside.}
Devo pisciare. La farò fuori.

[PISS2]
{Man, I gotta take a piss.}
Merda, devo pisciare.

[DOR1A1]
{You're doing fine, Cash, just fine. We're getting some great material here! Keep going!}
Stai facendo davvero un buon lavoro, Cash. Stiamo mettendo assieme del buon materiale. Continua così.

[DOR2A1]
{There's a Hood upstairs. Make some noise - hit something - that should get his attention!}
C'è un Hood di sopra. Fai rumore... colpisci qualcosa... che possa attirare la sua attenzione.

[DOR3A1]
{You're going to have to find something to bust that padlock!}
Devi trovare qualcosa per rompere il lucchetto.

[DOR4A1]
{A crowbar! That would be ideal for...}
Un piede di porco! sarebbe l'ideale per...

[DOR4A2]
{smashing a padlock, say!}
rompere il lucchetto, non credi?!

[DOR5A1]
{Okay, this is what I like to call a 'set up'.}
Ok, questo è ciò che si dice 'organizzazione'!

[DOR5A2]
{This guy will fight dirty, but once you're through with him, I'll open the next door.}
Quest'uomo combatterà in maniera sleale. Una volta che l'avrai superato, aprirò la prossima porta.

[DER1A1]
Director : Go through that building up ahead to get to the street.

[DER2A1]
Director : That hunter is watching the stairs, lure him downstairs by hitting a wall, then wait in a safe zone.

[DER3A1]
Director : This door is padlocked. You ever want to get outta here alive, you better find a way to bust that padlock!

[DER4A1]
Director : Okay Cash, nice going. Now Grab the crowbar and head back to smash that padlock.

[DER5A1]
Director : Okayyy, Put on a good show against this hooded fuck for me and it might help you outta here. Watch tho' this guy fights dirty.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!