[GOAL1]
Get to the street

[GOAL2]
Find something to break the ~blue~PADLOCK~colour~

[GOAL3]
Use the CROWBAR to break the ~blue~PADLOCK~colour~

[GOAL4]
Win the fight in the cellar

[GOAL5]
Head through the buildings to get to the library

[GOAL6]
Go through the cellar to the exit

[START0]
You can look behind you by pressing down the Look Back button.

[START2]
~!~

[START1]
~!~

[BLUE]
One handed weapons like the Bat are ~blue~Blue ~colour~Objects. They are not lost after use but make noise during executions.

[SWAP]
You can select individual weapons using the four Inventory Item buttons, or cycle through them with the Inventory button.

[LOOK]
Hold down the First Person button to view your surroundings. You can use this to spot hunters at a distance.

[SMASH]
Select the crowbar then press the Use button to break the padlock.

[GRAB]
Press the Action and the Action2 buttons together to grapple. Time the attack right and you can chain 3 hits together.

[GRAB2]
To break free from a hunter's grapple press the Action button repeatedly.

[BAT]
The bigger weapons are stronger but not as fast as the lighter weapons like the crowbar.

[TRIAN]
The Crowbar can be used to break padlocks and other locked objects.

[GRAVE]
Walking on gravel will make noise that attracts the hunters.

[WBAT]
Big weapons like this Baseball Bat are ~red~RED ~colour~items. They are stronger, but not as fast as the lighter weapons.

[BREAK]
Special Windows like this one can be smashed. They will create a glass shard for you to collect.

[RADAR]
Objectives are shown as a dot on the radar.

[PISS]
Hunter : I'm taking a leak, I'll be out in the alley.

[PISS1]
I need a leak. I'll be outside.

[PISS2]
Man, I gotta take a piss.

[DOR1A1]
You're doing fine, Cash, just fine. We're getting some great material here! Keep going!

[DOR2A1]
There's a Hood upstairs. Make some noise - hit something - that should get his attention!

[DOR3A1]
You're going to have to find something to bust that padlock!

[DOR4A1]
A crowbar! That would be ideal for...

[DOR4A2]
smashing a padlock, say!

[DOR5A1]
Okay, this is what I like to call a 'set up'.

[DOR5A2]
This guy will fight dirty, but once you're through with him, I'll open the next door.

[DER1A1]
Director : Go through that building up ahead to get to the street.

[DER2A1]
Director : That hunter is watching the stairs, lure him downstairs by hitting a wall, then wait in a safe zone.

[DER3A1]
Director : This door is padlocked. You ever want to get outta here alive, you better find a way to bust that padlock!

[DER4A1]
Director : Okay Cash, nice going. Now Grab the crowbar and head back to smash that padlock.

[DER5A1]
Director : Okayyy, Put on a good show against this hooded fuck for me and it might help you outta here. Watch tho' this guy fights dirty.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!