[GOAL1]
{Get to the street}
Consigue llegar a la calle.

[GOAL2]
{Find something to break the ~blue~PADLOCK~colour~}
Encuentra algo para romper el ~blue~CANDADO~colour~.

[GOAL3]
{Use the CROWBAR to break the ~blue~PADLOCK~colour~}
Utiliza la PALANCA para romper el ~blue~CANDADO~colour~.

[GOAL4]
{Win the fight in the cellar}
Gana el combate en el sótano.

[GOAL5]
{Head through the buildings to get to the library}
Atraviesa los edificios para llegar a la biblioteca.

[GOAL6]
{Go through the cellar to the exit}
Atraviesa el sótano hasta llegar a la salida.

[START0]
{You can look behind you by pressing down the Look Back button.}
Puedes mirar detrás de ti pulsando el botón Mirar atrás.

[START2]
~!~

[START1]
~!~

[BLUE]
{One handed weapons like the Bat are ~blue~Blue ~colour~Objects. They are not lost after use but make noise during executions.}
Las armas a una mano, como el bate, son objetos ~blue~azules ~colour~. No se pierden después de usarse, pero hacen ruido durante las ejecuciones.

[SWAP]
{You can select individual weapons using the four Inventory Item buttons, or cycle through them with the Inventory button.}
Puedes seleccionar armas individuales usando cuatro botones de Objeto de inventario, o cambiar entre ellas con el botón de Inventario.

[LOOK]
{Hold down the First Person button to view your surroundings. You can use this to spot hunters at a distance.}
Deja pulsado el botón Primera persona para mirar por los alrededores. Puedes usarlo para localizar a los cazadores desde lejos.

[SMASH]
{Select the crowbar then press the Use button to break the padlock.}
Selecciona la palanca y pulsa el botón Usar para romper el candado.

[GRAB]
{Press the Action and the Action2 buttons together to grapple. Time the attack right and you can chain 3 hits together.}
Para agarrar, pulsa a la vez los botones Acción y Acción2. Si sincronizas bien el ataque, puedes encadenar 3 golpes.

[GRAB2]
{To break free from a hunter's grapple press the Action button repeatedly.}
Para liberarte de la presa de un cazador, pulsa repetidamente el botón Acción.

[BAT]
{The bigger weapons are stronger but not as fast as the lighter weapons like the crowbar.}
Las armas más grandes son más fuertes pero no tan rápidas como las más ligeras, como la palanca.

[TRIAN]
{The Crowbar can be used to break padlocks and other locked objects.}
Se puede usar la palanca para romper candados y otros objetos cerrados.

[GRAVE]
{Walking on gravel will make noise that attracts the hunters.}
Moverse sobre grava hace ruido que puede atraer a los cazadores.

[WBAT]
{Big weapons like this Baseball Bat are ~red~RED ~colour~items. They are stronger, but not as fast as the lighter weapons.}
Las armas grandes, como el bate de béisbol, son objetos ~red~ROJOS~colour~. Son más fuertes, pero no tan rápidas como las armas más ligeras.

[BREAK]
{Special Windows like this one can be smashed. They will create a glass shard for you to collect.}
Las ventanas especiales, como ésta, pueden romperse. Se crearán fragmentos de cristal que puedes recoger.

[RADAR]
{Objectives are shown as a dot on the radar.}
Los objetivos se muestran en el radar en forma de punto.

[PISS]
{Hunter : I'm taking a leak, I'll be out in the alley.}
Cazador: Voy a cambiarle el agua al canario, estaré en el callejón.

[PISS1]
{I need a leak. I'll be outside.}
Tengo que regar las plantas. Estaré fuera.

[PISS2]
{Man, I gotta take a piss.}
Tío, tengo que echar un meo.

[DOR1A1]
{You're doing fine, Cash, just fine. We're getting some great material here! Keep going!}
Cash, ¡lo estás haciendo bien, bastante bien! ¡Muy buen material, sigue así!

[DOR2A1]
{There's a Hood upstairs. Make some noise - hit something - that should get his attention!}
Arriba hay un Hood. ¡Si haces algo de ruido (golpeando algo), deberías llamar su atención!

[DOR3A1]
{You're going to have to find something to bust that padlock!}
¡Vas a tener que buscar algo para forzar ese candado!

[DOR4A1]
{A crowbar! That would be ideal for...}
¡Una palanca! Sería ideal para...

[DOR4A2]
{smashing a padlock, say!}
forzar un candado, ¡claro!

[DOR5A1]
{Okay, this is what I like to call a 'set up'.}
Vale, eso es lo que yo llamo una emboscada.

[DOR5A2]
{This guy will fight dirty, but once you're through with him, I'll open the next door.}
Este tío luchará sucio, pero cuando acabes con él, abriré la siguiente puerta.

[DER1A1]
Director : Go through that building up ahead to get to the street.

[DER2A1]
Director : That hunter is watching the stairs, lure him downstairs by hitting a wall, then wait in a safe zone.

[DER3A1]
Director : This door is padlocked. You ever want to get outta here alive, you better find a way to bust that padlock!

[DER4A1]
Director : Okay Cash, nice going. Now Grab the crowbar and head back to smash that padlock.

[DER5A1]
Director : Okayyy, Put on a good show against this hooded fuck for me and it might help you outta here. Watch tho' this guy fights dirty.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!