[NOISE1]
VOICES SCREAMING: Man down, I need backup here! ARGH!!!!!

[CERB1]
CERBERUS: What the hell was THAT?

[CERB2]
CERBERUS: Holy SHIT!

[HTLK1]
CERBERUS: He's gone in there.

[HTLK2]
CERBERUS2: Who's got the fucking remote control?!?

[CERB3]
RADIO: A kill team is en route to your position.

[CERB4]
CERBERUS: Shoot targets on sight!, Starkweather want's them both dead.

[CERB5]
CERBERUS: No sign of either target, they won't get through this way!

[DEAD1]
CERBERUS : Ah these guys have been slaughtered, What the fuck did this?

[CERB6]
CERBERUS: Who shut this door?

[GOAL1]
You must find the side entrance to the mansion cellar

[PIGSY1]
What the-? Back up! I need immediate backupaarrgghh!

[PIGSY2]
Holy fuck! Gimme some help here-aarrgghh!

[PIGSY3]
Eerr, control, I'm gonna need some backup here! Control? Aarrgghh!

[REMOT1]
Who's got the fucking remote for the door?!?

[REMOT2]
Somebody get this damned door open!

[REMOT3]
Ok, who's got the remote - we gotta open this door!

[WHAT]
What the hell was that?!?

[SHIT]
Holy shit!

[INGAR1]
He's gone in there!

[INGAR2]
He's locked himself in the garage!

[INGAR3]
He's holed up in there!

[ENRTE1]
A team is en route to your position, over.

[ENRTE2]
We're sending a backup team, over.

[ENRTE3]
Hang in there, backup is on its way.

[KILL1]
Bring 'em down! Starkweather wants 'em both dead.

[KILL2]
Shoot to kill, repeat, shoot to kill - Both targets!

[KILL3]
Starkweather wants 'em both taken out!

[SNIPE1]
No sign of either target, they won't get through this way!

[SNIPE2]
I got my sector covered - nobody's coming through this way!

[SNIPE3]
The angel of death is home and awaiting visitors!

[SHUT1]
Who shut this door?

[SHUT2]
Hold on - this door was open a moment ago!

[SHUT3]
Hey wait a minute, wasn't this open?

[MPG1]
...but Mr. Starkweather refuses to comment on these allegations.

[MPG2]
At this point it is unclear as to whether or not he will ever be allowed to direct again.

[MPG3]
This is Rob...

[MPG4]
You know what?

[MPG5]
You know what? I don't give a fuck what Starkweather wants.

[MPG6]
Maybe today I kill you, maybe not.

[MPG7]
Kill the camera.

[MPG8]
What was that? Go check it out.

[MPG9]
Maybe it is your day.

[MPG10]
Shit, what the fuck is THAT?

[MPG11]
Support, repeat, send in...

[MPG12]
oh shit...

[MPG13]
AAHHHH! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!

[MPG14]
Keep an eye on him for a minute.

[MPG15]
Piggsy Angry!

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!