[GOD1]
Take the Journalist to her apartment. When you are close, press the Use button to make her wait or follow.

[GOD2]
Do not leave her too far behind, or she will get scared and will run to you!

[GOD3]
The doors of this police van can be opened with a crowbar. If you have one, face them and press the Use button.

[GOD4]
The journalist is freaking out! You have 20 seconds to go back to her or she will come looking for you!

[GOD5]
You need the journalist to open this door.

[GOD6]
Be careful to hide dead bodies. Cops will shoot on sight if they see a dead police officer.

[GOD7]
You have left the Journalist behind again!

[GOAL1]
Take the Journalist to her apartment and recover the dossier

[GOAL2]
Break out of the perimeter created by the Police and reach the SUBWAY

[BITCH1]
There's that reporter bitch! Hey you, don't move another inch!

[BITCH2]
Hey, lady! Stay where you are!

[BITCH3]
Hey you! You're wanted for questioning!

[GEN1]
Stay here, I'll check that!

[GEN2]
Wait here.

[GEN3]
Aww, what now? I'll check it out.

[GEN4]
What the hell is going on here??

[GEN5]
Someone is playing games with us. Let's check it out..

[GEN6]
What is up with that thing?

[MANDN1]
Dispatch, we have a man down! Fugitive is armed !

[MANDN2]
Dispatch, subject located, he is armed and dangerous!

[BITCH4]
There she is, that's her!

[BITCH5]
Hey, that's that reporter lady!

[BITCH6]
Hey, reporter lady, we want to talk to you!

[MANDN3]
Man down! Man down! Fugitive is to be considered highly dangerous!

[MANDN4]
Dispatch, I've located the fugitive! He's A&D!

[GEN7]
Hey, you ok down there? ...hey!

[GEN8]
You're sure taking your time...

[GEN9]
Hey, what's up? Talk to me, buddy, you're making me nervous!

[GEN10]
Come on, lets flush that bastard out!

[GEN11]
We better go see what's going on.

[GEN12]
Let's not get left out of all the fun.

[COV1]
Shit. Shit. Shit. We got plenty big trouble!

[COV2]
Covering fire!

[DISP1]
This is dispatch. Seal the perimeter. Snipers have been ordered to move in.

[CASIN1]
Officer down! Target has entered the casino!

[CASIN2]
Target sighted! Repeat, target sighted!

[CASIN3]
Man down! Man down! Target is approaching the casino!

[DISP2]
Sniper one please report your position...

[ALONE1]
Hey don't leave me alone!

[ALONE2]
Don't you desert me!

[ALONE3]
Hey, I thought we were sticking together!

[DOSS1]
Hey where are you going! Don't you want the dossier?!?

[DOSS2]
Take the dossier, for christ's sake!

[DOSS3]
You gonna leave the dossier? Take it!

[JFLAT1]
My place is upstairs. Here, I got the keys.

[JFLAT2]
My place is up a floor. Hold on, I'll just unlock the door...

[JFLAT3]
I'll get the door. My place's just up some stairs.

[JGUN1]
Great, a gun looks straight forward enough.

[JGUN2]
Ok, I've used a pistol before. Now where's the safety?

[JGUN3]
Alright, a gun! None of those freaks are gonna fuck with me now!

[JHLTH1]
These babies should numb the pain.

[JHLTH2]
I'm not usually a 'pill popper' but given the circumstances...

[JHLTH3]
Aahh, sweet pharmaceutical relief...

[JFLLW1]
Whatever you say...

[JFLLW2]
Ok, if you think it's safe

[JFLLW3]
Ok, but you gotta watch out for me!

[JFLLW4]
You got it - I'll stay close!

[JFLLW5]
You're the boss!

[JFLLW6]
I'm with you - lead the way.

[JSTAY1]
Ok, just dont leave me behind!

[JSTAY2]
You come back for me, ok!

[JSTAY3]
Alright, but don't be long!

[JSTAY4]
If you hear me scream, you better come back for me, ok?

[JSTAY5]
Ok, but you better not bug out on me!

[JSTAY6]
Ok, I'm counting on you!

[FREAK1]
I told you not to leave me alone!

[FREAK2]
Were you ever going to come back for me?

[FREAK3]
Don't leave me alone for that long again!

[PHEW1]
Thank God - I thought you'd just dumped me here!

[PHEW2]
I thought you were never coming back!

[PHEW3]
At last! Where have you been?

[CMON7]
You coming or what?

[CMON8]
Move your butt!

[CMON9]
C'mon, lady.

[CMON10]
Stick close and keep it quiet.

[CMON11]
I'll lead the way

[CMON12]
Move when I move.

[HOLD7]
I'll be back soon

[HOLD8]
Lay low here for a while.

[HOLD9]
Stay here, out of trouble.

[HOLD10]
Hold tight, I'll be right back.

[HOLD11]
Hold up.

[HOLD12]
I'll check ahead.

[JCUT1]
Everything I need is in that box under the table.

[JCUT2]
Good, take it and get out of town.

[JCUT3]
But... You're not coming with me!

[JCUT4]
I'm going to deal with Starkweather personally,

[JCUT5]
thank him for my 'second chance'.

[JCUT6]
You're my backup if I don't make it. Have a nice life.

[MPG1]
I've lost him.

[MPG2]
What? Are you fucking kiddin...

[MPG3]
Oh shut up! Get some of your boys to take care of it.

[MPG4]
Don't file the arrest report. Don't kill him either. Send both to me.

[MPG5]
Hey, remember who you're talking to, you son of a...

[MPG6]
Listen you fuck. It's your job to clean up this city's mess.

[MPG7]
That's what you get paid for.

[MPG8]
Shit.

[MPG9]
Ok, pull over here.

[MPG10]
But it's another block or two to my apartment!

[MPG11]
Just shut up and stick with me if you want to stay alive.

[JOUR2]
Come on, let's get that dossier.

[JOUR3]
Hey wait! We still have to get the dossier!

[JOUR4]
That is the stuff you wanted. Now leave.

[JOUR5]
My apartment is upstairs. I have to open this door first.

[AID]
These painkillers will make me fell a bit better.

[DIA1_1]
SHIT. SHIT. SHIT. THIS MEANS TROUBLE, MAN!

[DIA1_2]
THIS IS DISPATCH. SEAL THE PERIMETER. SNIPERS HAVE BEEN ORDERED TO MOVE IN.

[DIA1_3]
Come on, let's flush him out.

[DIA2_1]
MAN DOWN! MAN DOWN! TARGET IS INSIDE THE CASINO!

[DIA2_2]
TARGET SIGHTED! REPEAT, TARGET SIGHTED!

[DIA2_3]
COVERING FIRE!!!

[DIA2_4]
COVERING FIRE!!!

[DIA2_5]
MAN DOWN! MAN DOWN! TARGET IS APPROACHING THE CASINO!

[DIA2_6]
SNIPER1 PLEASE REPORT YOUR POSITION...

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!