[COVER]
{Certain objects can be used to wall-strafe against. Press the Use button when near a wall or object to wall-strafe.}
Tu peux te coller à certains objets. Appuie sur la touche Utiliser quand t'es près d'un mur ou d'un objet pour t'y plaquer.

[SHOOT]
{While in wall-strafe mode press the Action2 button to aim over the object or to the side.}
Appuie sur la touche "Action 2" pour viser par-dessus ou sur le côté de l'objet que tu colles.

[LOCK]
{This door wont budge, try shooting off the lock.}
Cette porte bougera pas, essaie de tirer sur la serrure.

[BAR]
{Go to the basement in the bar.}
Va dans le bar, au sous-sol.

[GOAL1]
{Get your hands on a gun}
Chope un flingue.

[GOAL2]
{Find the video tape}
Trouve la cassette.

[GOAL3]
{Find the video camera}
Trouve la caméra.

[GOAL4]
{Go watch the video on the bar TV}
Va regarder la cassette sur la TV du bar.

[GOAL5]
{Go to the bar basement and turn on the power}
Va au bar, au sous-sol, et allume le magnétoscope.

[FAL1A1]
{So, how are we doing, Cash? Enjoying it so far?}
Alors, comment ça va, Cash ? Tu t'éclates ?

[FAL1A2]
{I thought you could do with a little R&R, so I've arranged a special}
Je me disais que tu voudrais te détendre, alors j'ai organisé une petite

[FAL1A3]
{screening... just for you...}
avant-première... rien que pour toi...

[FAL1A4]
{It's work in progress, but I think you'll appreciate it.}
On a pas tout à fait fini mais je crois que ça va te plaire.

[FAL13A1]
{I've hidden the tape and a video camera in the Mall. Find them.}
J'ai planqué la cassette et une caméra dans le centre commercial. Trouve-les !

[FAL2A1]
{By the way, these guys are packing heat, so you might want to find a gun for yourself.}
Au fait, ces mecs sont enfouraillés jusqu'aux yeux, alors trouve-toi une pétoire à toi.

[FAL3A1]
{Ok, we're cooking with gas now! Go find that tape!}
OK, ça va pas tarder à péter ! Va chercher la cassette !

[FAL4A1]
{Now all you need is the camera.}
Il te manque plus que la caméra.

[FAL5A1]
{Aw hell, that's the camera with the broken screen! I told those guys...}
Merde, l'écran de cette caméra est bousillé ! Je leur avais pourtant dit...

[FAL5A2]
{No problem, there's a TV in a bar somewhere around here.}
Bon, c'est pas grave, il y a une télé dans un bar pas loin d'ici.

[FAL6A1]
{Does nothing fucking work round here?}
Mais y'a donc rien qui marche ici ?

[FAL7A1]
{You're gonna have to see if you can turn on the power in the basement.}
Va falloir que t'ailles au sous-sol, voir si tu peux remettre le jus.

[FAL8A1]
{Beautifully done, Cash, now just toddle back up to the bar and enjoy the show.}
Magnifique, Cash ! T'as plus qu'à retourner au bar et t'installer pour admirer le spectacle !

[FAL9A1]
{You must understand, Cash, I could never have let them go.}
Faut que tu comprennes, Cash, je pouvais pas les laisser partir.

[FAL10A1]
{You must understand, Cash, I could never have let him go.}
Faut que tu comprennes, Cash, je pouvais pas le laisser partir.

[FAL11A1]
{You must understand, Cash, I could never have let her go.}
Faut que tu comprennes, Cash, je pouvais pas la laisser partir.

[FAL12A1]
{Where were your family when you were facing your final moments in the chamber anyway?}
Elle était où, ta famille, quand t'attendais ta dernière heure dans le couloir de la mort ?

[FAL12A2]
{And what gratitude did they show you when you saved them from those gung-ho assholes, eh?}
Et est-ce qu'ils t'ont remercié quand tu les as sauvés de ces acharnés de la gâchette ?

[FAL12A3]
{You've left your old life, your old self, behind.}
T'as laissé ton ancienne vie derrière toi, Cash.

[FAL12A4]
{I'm all the family you need now.}
T'as plus que moi, maintenant.

[MPG1]
{You! Get out to the graveyard!}
Toi ! Va au cimetière !

[MPG2]
{You and you! I want you up there!}
Toi et toi ! Je vous veux là-haut !

[MPG3]
{And I want you to follow him over to the Mall...}
Et toi, je veux que tu le suives au centre commercial...

[MPG4]
{NOW FUCKING MOVE!!}
ALLEZ, MAGNEZ-VOUS !

[MPG5]
Putain, quelle merde !

[ENT1]
So, how are we doing, Cash? enjoying it so far?

[ENT2]
I thought you could do with a little R & R, so I've arranged a special screening just for you.

[ENT3]
It's a work in progress, but I think you'll appreciate it.

[ENT4]
I've hidden the tape and a video camera in the mall, find them

[GUN]
By the way, these guys are packing heat, so you might want to find a gun yourself, before you venture too far...

[CAMVHS]
Ok, we're cooking with gas now! go and find that tape!

[GTAPE]
Now all you need is the camera...

[GBOTH]
Aw hell, that's the camera with the broken screen! I told those guys...

[GBOTH2]
Not a problem, there's a TV in a bar around here someplace

[INBAR]
Does nothing fucking work around here?

[CELLAR]
You're gonna have to see if you can turn the power on in the basement.

[ENDTHEM]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let them go.

[ENDHIM]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let him go.

[ENDHER]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let her go.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!