[COVER]
Certain objects can be used to wall-strafe against. Press the Use button when near a wall or object to wall-strafe.

[SHOOT]
While in wall-strafe mode press the Action2 button to aim over the object or to the side.

[LOCK]
This door wont budge, try shooting off the lock.

[BAR]
Go to the basement in the bar.

[GOAL1]
Get your hands on a gun

[GOAL2]
Find the video tape

[GOAL3]
Find the video camera

[GOAL4]
Go watch the video on the bar TV

[GOAL5]
Go to the bar basement and turn on the power

[FAL1A1]
So, how are we doing, Cash? Enjoying it so far?

[FAL1A2]
I thought you could do with a little R&R, so I've arranged a special

[FAL1A3]
screening... just for you...

[FAL1A4]
It's work in progress, but I think you'll appreciate it.

[FAL13A1]
I've hidden the tape and a video camera in the Mall. Find them.

[FAL2A1]
By the way, these guys are packing heat, so you might want to find a gun for yourself.

[FAL3A1]
Ok, we're cooking with gas now! Go find that tape!

[FAL4A1]
Now all you need is the camera.

[FAL5A1]
Aw hell, that's the camera with the broken screen! I told those guys...

[FAL5A2]
No problem, there's a TV in a bar somewhere around here.

[FAL6A1]
Does nothing fucking work round here?

[FAL7A1]
You're gonna have to see if you can turn on the power in the basement.

[FAL8A1]
Beautifully done, Cash, now just toddle back up to the bar and enjoy the show.

[FAL9A1]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let them go.

[FAL10A1]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let him go.

[FAL11A1]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let her go.

[FAL12A1]
Where were your family when you were facing your final moments in the chamber anyway?

[FAL12A2]
And what gratitude did they show you when you saved them from those gung-ho assholes, eh?

[FAL12A3]
You've left your old life, your old self, behind.

[FAL12A4]
I'm all the family you need now.

[MPG1]
You! Get out to the graveyard!

[MPG2]
You and you! I want you up there!

[MPG3]
And I want you to follow him over to the Mall...

[MPG4]
NOW FUCKING MOVE!!

[ENT1]
So, how are we doing, Cash? enjoying it so far?

[ENT2]
I thought you could do with a little R & R, so I've arranged a special screening just for you.

[ENT3]
It's a work in progress, but I think you'll appreciate it.

[ENT4]
I've hidden the tape and a video camera in the mall, find them

[GUN]
By the way, these guys are packing heat, so you might want to find a gun yourself, before you venture too far...

[CAMVHS]
Ok, we're cooking with gas now! go and find that tape!

[GTAPE]
Now all you need is the camera...

[GBOTH]
Aw hell, that's the camera with the broken screen! I told those guys...

[GBOTH2]
Not a problem, there's a TV in a bar around here someplace

[INBAR]
Does nothing fucking work around here?

[CELLAR]
You're gonna have to see if you can turn the power on in the basement.

[ENDTHEM]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let them go.

[ENDHIM]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let him go.

[ENDHER]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let her go.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!