[KEY]
{You have collected the ELEVATOR KEY.}
T'as récupéré la CLEF DE L'ASCENSEUR.

[KEY2]
{The Cerberus Leader has dropped the ~green~ELEVATOR KEY~colour~, go and get it!}
Le chef des Cerbères a lâché la ~green~CLE DE L'ASCENSEUR~colour~. Va la chercher !

[CAMERA]
{You have been spotted by a SECURITY CAMERA - The guards will know your position now.}
T'as été repéré par une CAMERA. Les gardes savent où t'es maintenant !

[CAMERA2]
{Watch out for SECURITY CAMERAS. The Cerberus guards use them to know where you are.}
Gaffe aux CAMERAS ! Les Cerbères les utilisent pour te repérer.

[LIFT]
{The ELEVATOR is now operational again.}
L'ASCENSEUR marche à nouveau!

[GOD1]
{You cannot use the elevator yet. You don't have the KEY and the POWER is still off.}
Tu peux toujours pas utiliser l'ascenseur. T'as pas la CLEF et le COURANT est toujours coupé.

[GOD2]
{You cannot use the elevator yet. You don't have the KEY.}
Tu peux toujours pas utiliser l'ascenseur. T'as pas la CLEF.

[GOD3]
{You cannot use the elevator yet. The POWER is still off.}
Tu peux toujours pas utiliser l'ascenseur. Le COURANT est pas rétabli.

[GOAL1]
{Find the ~green~LEADER~colour~ of the Cerberus team and acquire the ELEVATOR KEY}
Trouve le ~green~CHEF~colour~ des Cerbères et chope la CLEF DE L'ASCENSEUR.

[GOAL2]
{Reach the ~blue~basement~colour~ in the west wing and turn Starkweather's ELEVATOR back on}
Va au ~blue~sous-sol~colour~ de l'aile ouest et rétablis le courant de l'ASCENSEUR de Starkweather.

[GOAL3]
{Use the ELEVATOR to reach Starkweather}
Prends l'ASCENSEUR pour atteindre Starkweather.

[SUPRT1]
{Copy that request for support! Hang in there guys, help is coming!}
Demande de renforts confirmée ! Tenez bon les gars, les renforts arrivent !

[SUPRT2]
{Roger that! Reinforcements are on their way!}
Compris ! Les renforts sont en route !

[SUPRT3]
{Wilco, should be with you guys ASAP!}
OK, on arrive tout de suite !

[CNV1_1]
{Sir, one of the men is not responding. We have to move you somewhere more secure.}
Monsieur, un de nos hommes répond plus. Nous devons vous mettre en sécurité.

[CNV1_2]
{I want that asshole's head on a spike, sergeant!}
Je veux la tête de ce trou du cul sur une pique, sergent !

[CNV1_3]
{It will be a pleasure, sir! Escort him upstairs.}
Avec plaisir, monsieur ! Escortez-le en haut.

[CNV2_1]
{How did that psycho bastard get past the perimeter guards?}
Comment ce taré a pu passer les gardes de l'entrée ?

[CNV2_2]
{Cash has already neutralised two of our snipers, sir. We should assume he is armed.}
Cash a déjà neutralisé deux des snipers, monsieur. Faut croire qu'il est armé.

[CNV2_3]
{Leave two of your best men in the basement, I don't want any more surprises.}
Laissez deux de vos meilleurs hommes au sous-sol. Je veux plus de mauvaises surprises.

[CNV2_4]
{Already taken care of, sir. All the men are ready.}
C'est déjà fait, monsieur. Tous les hommes sont prêts !

[CNV2_5]
{I have instructed them to equip themselves from the armoury.}
Je leur ai donné ordre de se servir dans l'armurerie.

[CNV2_6]
{Very well. Any sign of him on the security cameras?}
Parfait. Aucun signe de lui sur les caméras ?

[CNV2_7]
{No sir, but if he gets anywhere near that elevator we will be right on him.}
Non, monsieur. Mais s'il s'approche de cet ascenseur, il n'en sortira pas vivant !

[LIFT1]
{Shut the lift down, Starkweather said no unexpected visitors.}
Coupez le courant de l'ascenseur. Starkweather n'attend aucune visite.

[LIFT2]
{Roger.}
OK.

[GUN1]
{Target is armed! Keep him confined!}
La cible est armée ! Retenez-la !

[NOGUN1]
{Target is not armed! Flush him so we can take him out!}
La cible n'est pas armée ! Faites-le sortir pour qu'on le descende !

[HEAVY1]
{What the? -oh shit!!!}
Qu'est-ce que... ? Et merde !

[HEAVY2]
{Holy fuck! He's packing heavy!}
Putain ! Il a de l'artillerie !

[HEAVY3]
{Take cover, he means business!}
A couvert ! Il rigole pas !

[STORM1]
{Fuck this, I'm going in!!!!}
Rien à foutre, j'y vais !

[STORM2]
{I'm coming in there to fuck you up!!!}
Je viens te régler ton compte, connard !

[STORM3]
{Who dares, wins - rraagghh!!!}
On a rien sans rien ! Raaaggghh !

[MPG1]
{Have you locked the elevator?}
Vous avez verrouillé l'ascenseur ?

[MPG2]
{Nobody gets anywhere near Starkweather. Give me the key.}
Personne ne s'approche de Starkweather ! Donnez-moi la clef.

[MPG3]
{Yes sir.}
Oui, monsieur.

[MPG4]
{I want you to go down to the basement and turn off the motor.}
Allez au sous-sol et coupez le générateur.

[MPG5]
{We can't be safe with these two bastards running around.}
Personne n'est en sécurité avec ces deux tarés dans les parages.

[MPG6]
{We're on it, sir.}
On s'en occupe, monsieur.

[GEN]
{RADIO VOICE: We have reported casualties! Hang tough guys, reinforcements on their way!}
RADIO VOICE: Nous avons demandé de laide ! Accrochez-vous les gars, les renforts arrivent !

[CERB1]
GUARD: Shut the lift down, Strarkweather said no unexpected visitors.

[CERB2]
GUARD: Roger. (Pulls lever).

[CERB3]
GUARD: Sir, One of the men is not responding. We have to take you somewhere more secure.

[CHF1]
CHIEF: Order the men to shoot at anything that moves.

[CERB4]
GUARD: Consider it done, sir. Escort him upstairs.

[CHF2]
CHIEF: How did that bastard get past the perimeter guards?

[CERB5]
GUARD: He has killed two of our snipers, sir. We should assume he is armed.

[CHF3]
CHIEF: I want his head on a silver plate, seargent!

[CERB6]
GUARD: All men are ready, I have instructed them to equip themselves from the armoury.

[CHF4]
CHIEF: Very well. Any sign of him in the security cameras?

[CERB7]
GUARD: No sir, but if he gets anywhere near that elevator we will be right on him

[CHF5]
CHIEF: Leave two of your best men in the basement, I don't want more surprise.

[CERB8]
GUARD: This has been already taken care of, sir.

[BAS1]
GUARD: OH SHIT!!!

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!