[COVER]
{Certain objects can be used to wall-strafe against. Press the Use button when near a wall or object to wall-strafe.}
Algunos objetos pueden usarse para moverse pegado a ellos. Pulsa el botón Usar cuando estés cerca de una pared o un objeto para moverte pegado a la superficie.

[SHOOT]
{While in wall-strafe mode press the Action2 button to aim over the object or to the side.}
Mientras estés en modo de movimiento pegado a la pared, pulsa el Acción2 para apuntar al objeto o a un lado.

[LOCK]
{This door wont budge, try shooting off the lock.}
Esta puerta no va a ceder, prueba a volar la cerradura de un disparo.

[BAR]
{Go to the basement in the bar.}
Ve al sótano del bar.

[GOAL1]
{Get your hands on a gun}
Consigue un arma

[GOAL2]
{Find the video tape}
Encuentra la cinta de vídeo

[GOAL3]
{Find the video camera}
Encuentra la cámara de vídeo

[GOAL4]
{Go watch the video on the bar TV}
Ve a ver el vídeo en la tele del bar

[GOAL5]
{Go to the bar basement and turn on the power}
Ve al sótano del bar y conecta la electricidad

[FAL1A1]
{So, how are we doing, Cash? Enjoying it so far?}
¿Qué tal vamos, Cash? ¿Te diviertes?

[FAL1A2]
{I thought you could do with a little R&R, so I've arranged a special}
Creí que podrías tomarte un descanso, así que he preparado una proyección

[FAL1A3]
{screening... just for you...}
especial... solo para ti...

[FAL1A4]
{It's work in progress, but I think you'll appreciate it.}
Es un trabajo no terminado, pero creo que sabrás apreciarlo.

[FAL13A1]
{I've hidden the tape and a video camera in the Mall. Find them.}
He escondido la cinta y una videocámara en el centro comercial. Encuéntralos.

[FAL2A1]
{By the way, these guys are packing heat, so you might want to find a gun for yourself.}
A todo esto, estos tíos van armados, así que seguramente querrás conseguir un arma para ti.

[FAL3A1]
{Ok, we're cooking with gas now! Go find that tape!}
Anda, ¡ahora sí que nos entendemos! ¡Ve a encontrar la cinta!

[FAL4A1]
{Now all you need is the camera.}
Ahora todo lo que necesitas es la cámara.

[FAL5A1]
{Aw hell, that's the camera with the broken screen! I told those guys...}
Maldición, ¡la cámara tiene la pantalla rota! Les dije a esos tíos...

[FAL5A2]
{No problem, there's a TV in a bar somewhere around here.}
No pasa nada, hay una tele en un bar, en algún lugar por aquí cerca.

[FAL6A1]
{Does nothing fucking work round here?}
¿Pero es que nada funciona por aquí, coño?

[FAL7A1]
{You're gonna have to see if you can turn on the power in the basement.}
Tendrás que ir a ver si puedes conectar la electricidad en el sótano.

[FAL8A1]
{Beautifully done, Cash, now just toddle back up to the bar and enjoy the show.}
¡Muy bien hecho, Cash, ahora solo tienes que volver al bar y disfrutar del espectáculo!

[FAL9A1]
{You must understand, Cash, I could never have let them go.}
Debes entenderlo, Cash, no habría podido dejarles marchar.

[FAL10A1]
{You must understand, Cash, I could never have let him go.}
Debes entenderlo, Cash, no habría podido dejarle marchar.

[FAL11A1]
{You must understand, Cash, I could never have let her go.}
Debes entenderlo, Cash, no habría podido dejarla marchar.

[FAL12A1]
{Where were your family when you were facing your final moments in the chamber anyway?}
De todas maneras, ¡¿dónde estaba tu familia cuando estabas afrontando tu destino en la cámara?!

[FAL12A2]
{And what gratitude did they show you when you saved them from those gung-ho assholes, eh?}
¿Y estuvieron agradecidos cuando los salvaste de esos estúpidos matones, eh?

[FAL12A3]
{You've left your old life, your old self, behind.}
Has dejado atrás tu antigua vida, has dejado atrás tu antiguo yo.

[FAL12A4]
{I'm all the family you need now.}
Ahora, yo soy toda la familia que necesitas.

[MPG1]
{You! Get out to the graveyard!}
¡Tú! ¡Sal del cementerio!

[MPG2]
{You and you! I want you up there!}
¡Tú y tú! ¡Os quiero allí!

[MPG3]
{And I want you to follow him over to the Mall...}
Y quiero que le sigáis hasta el centro comercial...

[MPG4]
{NOW FUCKING MOVE!!}
¡¡AHORA MUÉVETE DE UNA JODIDA VEZ!

[MPG5]
¡Mierda! Hijo de perra.

[ENT1]
So, how are we doing, Cash? enjoying it so far?

[ENT2]
I thought you could do with a little R & R, so I've arranged a special screening just for you.

[ENT3]
It's a work in progress, but I think you'll appreciate it.

[ENT4]
I've hidden the tape and a video camera in the mall, find them

[GUN]
By the way, these guys are packing heat, so you might want to find a gun yourself, before you venture too far...

[CAMVHS]
Ok, we're cooking with gas now! go and find that tape!

[GTAPE]
Now all you need is the camera...

[GBOTH]
Aw hell, that's the camera with the broken screen! I told those guys...

[GBOTH2]
Not a problem, there's a TV in a bar around here someplace

[INBAR]
Does nothing fucking work around here?

[CELLAR]
You're gonna have to see if you can turn the power on in the basement.

[ENDTHEM]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let them go.

[ENDHIM]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let him go.

[ENDHER]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let her go.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!