[KEY]
You have collected the ELEVATOR KEY.

[KEY2]
The Cerberus Leader has dropped the ~green~ELEVATOR KEY~colour~, go and get it!

[CAMERA]
You have been spotted by a SECURITY CAMERA - The guards will know your position now.

[CAMERA2]
Watch out for SECURITY CAMERAS. The Cerberus guards use them to know where you are.

[LIFT]
The ELEVATOR is now operational again.

[GOD1]
You cannot use the elevator yet. You don't have the KEY and the POWER is still off.

[GOD2]
You cannot use the elevator yet. You don't have the KEY.

[GOD3]
You cannot use the elevator yet. The POWER is still off.

[GOAL1]
Find the ~green~LEADER~colour~ of the Cerberus team and acquire the ELEVATOR KEY

[GOAL2]
Reach the ~blue~basement~colour~ in the west wing and turn Starkweather's ELEVATOR back on

[GOAL3]
Use the ELEVATOR to reach Starkweather

[SUPRT1]
Copy that request for support! Hang in there guys, help is coming!

[SUPRT2]
Roger that! Reinforcements are on their way!

[SUPRT3]
Wilco, should be with you guys ASAP!

[CNV1_1]
Sir, one of the men is not responding. We have to move you somewhere more secure.

[CNV1_2]
I want that asshole's head on a spike, sergeant!

[CNV1_3]
It will be a pleasure, sir! Escort him upstairs.

[CNV2_1]
How did that psycho bastard get past the perimeter guards?

[CNV2_2]
Cash has already neutralised two of our snipers, sir. We should assume he is armed.

[CNV2_3]
Leave two of your best men in the basement, I don't want any more surprises.

[CNV2_4]
Already taken care of, sir. All the men are ready.

[CNV2_5]
I have instructed them to equip themselves from the armoury.

[CNV2_6]
Very well. Any sign of him on the security cameras?

[CNV2_7]
No sir, but if he gets anywhere near that elevator we will be right on him.

[LIFT1]
Shut the lift down, Starkweather said no unexpected visitors.

[LIFT2]
Roger.

[GUN1]
Target is armed! Keep him confined!

[NOGUN1]
Target is not armed! Flush him so we can take him out!

[HEAVY1]
What the? -oh shit!!!

[HEAVY2]
Holy fuck! He's packing heavy!

[HEAVY3]
Take cover, he means business!

[STORM1]
Fuck this, I'm going in!!!!

[STORM2]
I'm coming in there to fuck you up!!!

[STORM3]
Who dares, wins - rraagghh!!!

[MPG1]
Have you locked the elevator?

[MPG2]
Nobody gets anywhere near Starkweather. Give me the key.

[MPG3]
Yes sir.

[MPG4]
I want you to go down to the basement and turn off the motor.

[MPG5]
We can't be safe with these two bastards running around.

[MPG6]
We're on it, sir.

[GEN]
RADIO VOICE: We have reported casualties! Hang tough guys, reinforcements on their way!

[CERB1]
GUARD: Shut the lift down, Strarkweather said no unexpected visitors.

[CERB2]
GUARD: Roger. (Pulls lever).

[CERB3]
GUARD: Sir, One of the men is not responding. We have to take you somewhere more secure.

[CHF1]
CHIEF: Order the men to shoot at anything that moves.

[CERB4]
GUARD: Consider it done, sir. Escort him upstairs.

[CHF2]
CHIEF: How did that bastard get past the perimeter guards?

[CERB5]
GUARD: He has killed two of our snipers, sir. We should assume he is armed.

[CHF3]
CHIEF: I want his head on a silver plate, seargent!

[CERB6]
GUARD: All men are ready, I have instructed them to equip themselves from the armoury.

[CHF4]
CHIEF: Very well. Any sign of him in the security cameras?

[CERB7]
GUARD: No sir, but if he gets anywhere near that elevator we will be right on him

[CHF5]
CHIEF: Leave two of your best men in the basement, I don't want more surprise.

[CERB8]
GUARD: This has been already taken care of, sir.

[BAS1]
GUARD: OH SHIT!!!

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!