[COVER]
{Certain objects can be used to wall-strafe against. Press the Use button when near a wall or object to wall-strafe.}
Per procedere furtivamente, premi il tasto Usa quando sei vicino a una parete o a un oggetto per appoggiarti.

[SHOOT]
{While in wall-strafe mode press the Action2 button to aim over the object or to the side.}
Quando ti appoggi a una parete, premi il tasto Azione2 per sbirciare dietro un angolo.

[LOCK]
{This door wont budge, try shooting off the lock.}
Questa porta non vuole aprirsi, prova a far saltare la serratura.

[BAR]
{Go to the basement in the bar.}
Raggiungi lo scantinato del bar.

[GOAL1]
{Get your hands on a gun}
Recupera una pistola.

[GOAL2]
{Find the video tape}
Trova il video.

[GOAL3]
{Find the video camera}
Trova la telecamera.

[GOAL4]
{Go watch the video on the bar TV}
Vai a guardare il video nella TV del bar.

[GOAL5]
{Go to the bar basement and turn on the power}
Scendi nello scantinato e ridai corrente al bar.

[FAL1A1]
{So, how are we doing, Cash? Enjoying it so far?}
Allora, come andiamo Cash? Ti sei divertito finora?

[FAL1A2]
{I thought you could do with a little R&R, so I've arranged a special}
Ho pensato che dovresti riposarti un po', così ho preparato una proiezione

[FAL1A3]
{screening... just for you...}
speciale... solo per te...

[FAL1A4]
{It's work in progress, but I think you'll appreciate it.}
È ancora in fase di lavorazione, ma penso che l'apprezzerai.

[FAL13A1]
{I've hidden the tape and a video camera in the Mall. Find them.}
Ho nascosto il filmato e una videocamera nel centro commerciale. Trovali.

[FAL2A1]
{By the way, these guys are packing heat, so you might want to find a gun for yourself.}
A proposito, questi ragazzi sono armati fino ai denti, quindi faresti meglio a procurarti una pistola.

[FAL3A1]
{Ok, we're cooking with gas now! Go find that tape!}
OK, la situazione si sta facendo bollente. Trova quel nastro!

[FAL4A1]
{Now all you need is the camera.}
Ora, tutto ciò che ti serve è una telecamera.

[FAL5A1]
{Aw hell, that's the camera with the broken screen! I told those guys...}
Maledizione, quella è la telecamera con lo schermo rotto! Avevo detto a quei ragazzi...

[FAL5A2]
{No problem, there's a TV in a bar somewhere around here.}
Nessun problema, c'è una TV in un bar qui vicino.

[FAL6A1]
{Does nothing fucking work round here?}
Ma non funziona proprio niente da queste parti?

[FAL7A1]
{You're gonna have to see if you can turn on the power in the basement.}
Devi cercare di riattivare la corrente nello scantinato.

[FAL8A1]
{Beautifully done, Cash, now just toddle back up to the bar and enjoy the show.}
Ben fatto, Cash, adesso torna al bar e goditi lo spettacolo!

[FAL9A1]
{You must understand, Cash, I could never have let them go.}
Cash, devi capire che non li avrei mai lasciati andare.

[FAL10A1]
{You must understand, Cash, I could never have let him go.}
Cash, devi capire che non l'avrei mai lasciato andare.

[FAL11A1]
{You must understand, Cash, I could never have let her go.}
Cash, devi capire che non l'avrei mai lasciata andare.

[FAL12A1]
{Where were your family when you were facing your final moments in the chamber anyway?}
E comunque, dov'era la tua famiglia quando stavi per essere giustiziato?

[FAL12A2]
{And what gratitude did they show you when you saved them from those gung-ho assholes, eh?}
E qual è stata la loro gratitudine quando li hai salvati da quel branco di maniaci?

[FAL12A3]
{You've left your old life, your old self, behind.}
Dimentica la tua vecchia vita, la tua vecchia identità.

[FAL12A4]
{I'm all the family you need now.}
Ora sono io la tua famiglia.

[MPG1]
{You! Get out to the graveyard!}
Ehi, voi! Raggiungete il cimitero!

[MPG2]
{You and you! I want you up there!}
Voi due! Vi voglio lassù!

[MPG3]
{And I want you to follow him over to the Mall...}
E voglio che lo seguiate fino al centro commerciale...

[MPG4]
{NOW FUCKING MOVE!!}
MUOVETEVI DANNAZIONE!!!

[MPG5]
Che grandissimo figlio di puttana!

[ENT1]
So, how are we doing, Cash? enjoying it so far?

[ENT2]
I thought you could do with a little R & R, so I've arranged a special screening just for you.

[ENT3]
It's a work in progress, but I think you'll appreciate it.

[ENT4]
I've hidden the tape and a video camera in the mall, find them

[GUN]
By the way, these guys are packing heat, so you might want to find a gun yourself, before you venture too far...

[CAMVHS]
Ok, we're cooking with gas now! go and find that tape!

[GTAPE]
Now all you need is the camera...

[GBOTH]
Aw hell, that's the camera with the broken screen! I told those guys...

[GBOTH2]
Not a problem, there's a TV in a bar around here someplace

[INBAR]
Does nothing fucking work around here?

[CELLAR]
You're gonna have to see if you can turn the power on in the basement.

[ENDTHEM]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let them go.

[ENDHIM]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let him go.

[ENDHER]
You must understand, Cash, I could never have let her go.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!! AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!