[PGKEY]
{You have picked up the PRISON GATE KEY.}
Tu as récupéré la CLEF DES PORTES DE LA PRISON.

[GOAL1]
{Follow the rabbit by exiting the cellblock}
Suis le lapin en sortant du bloc de détention.

[GOAL2]
{Kill the patrolling hunter and get up to the control room}
Trucide le chasseur en patrouille et monte à la salle de contrôle.

[GOAL3]
{Kill all the death row hunters}
Bute tous les chasseurs du couloir de la mort.

[GOAL4]
{Get to the workshop anyway you can}
Démerde-toi pour atteindre l'atelier.

[GOAL5]
{Activate the sensor lock and chase that rabbit}
Active le verrouillage et poursuis ce lapin.

[GOAL6]
{Kill the ~green~White Rabbit~colour~ to acquire the KEY to the prison's gates}
Tue le ~green~lapin blanc~colour~ pour choper la CLEF des portes de la prison.

[GOAL7]
{Get to the gates and exit the prison}
Va jusqu'aux portes et quitte la prison.

[SCREW1]
{Darling, I'm coming to get you!}
Bouge pas, chérie, j'arrive !

[COVER1]
{Take cover, you idiots!}
A couvert, bande de connards !

[COVER2]
{Take cover! Take cover!}
A couvert ! A couvert !

[COVER3]
{He's packing! Take cover!}
Il est armé ! A couvert !

[DIE1]
{You did well! Very well. But every film has its ending and this here is yours!}
T'es fort ! Très fort ! Mais tous les films ont une fin et pour toi, ce sera pas un happy end !

[DIE2]
{You made it! Oh dear, you see, you didn't make it after all! Ha-ha-heee-hooo!}
T'as réussi ! Oh, oups, en fait, non, désolé, trop bête... ah ah eh eh ho ho !

[DIE3]
{Close your eyes, bad boy! Time for bye-byes!}
Ferme les yeux, mon tout beau. C'est l'heure de faire dodo !

[OUT1]
{Hey, you ain't dead! He ain't dead! Oh shit, I've got the keys outta here!}
Hé, t'es pas mort ! Il est pas mort ! Et merde, j'ai la clef pour sortir d'ici !

[OUT2]
{You're supposed to be dead! Aw fuck, he's after my frikkin' key!}
Tu devais être mort ! Merde ! Il veut me piquer ma putain de clef !

[OUT3]
{Holy frogger! I've got the key - if he gets me he's outta here!}
Chiottes ! J'ai la clef ! S'il me chope, il est libre !

[POL1A1]
{You're my big ugly Alice, so go on, follow the White Rabbit!}
Tu es ma grosse Alice, alors vas-y, suis le lapin Blanc !

[POL2A1]
{They're messing with you, Cash, trying to fuck with your head! I wouldn't stand for that!}
Ils te cherchent des emmerdes, Cash ! A ta place, je me laisserais pas faire !

[POL3A1]
{You might want to clean the filth out of the showers...}
Faudrait récurer les douches, histoire de virer toute la merde...

[POL4A1]
{Get rid of the pink dressed freak and get up to the watch room. Mr. Rabbit has left you a gift!}
Débarrasse-toi du taré en rose et va à la salle d'observation. M'sieur le lapin t'a laissé un cadeau !

[POL5A1]
{A new meaning for death row! Get yourself up to that watch room!}
C'est pour ça qu'on l'appelle le couloir de la mort... Direction la salle d'observation !

[POL6A1]
{You're a threshing machine, Cash! Now head for the door below the control room!}
T'es un vrai déchiqueteur, Cash ! Maintenant va à la porte, sous la salle de contrôle !

[POL7A1]
{Watch those cells closely. Kill 'em all!}
Attention à ces cellules ! Tue-les tous !

[POL8A1]
{Almost there, baby! Chew your way through these chumps!}
Tu y es presque, mon mignon. Les laisse pas t'arrêter, bute-les !

[POL9A1]
{What can I say? You were a good leading man, the audience will love you.}
Que te dire ? Le public va t'adorer, t'es un vrai meneur d'hommes !

[POL9A2]
{Don't expect any royalty cheques where you're going though!}
Mais t'attends pas à recevoir des royalties là où tu vas...

[POL10A1]
{Hey, Cash, what are you doing? Are you insane?}
Hé, Cash. Qu'est-ce que tu fous ? T'es taré ou quoi ?

[POL11A1]
{Where are you gonna go? The state wants you dead, Cash, dead!}
Où tu vas aller ? T'es condamné à mort, Cash, A MORT !

[POL12A1]
{Cash? Come back here!}
Cash ? Reviens ici !

[MPG1]
{Ramirez!}
Ramirez !

[MPG2]
{You let Cash slip his leash - bring him to heel!}
T'as laissé Cash se tirer ! Ramène-le illico !

[MPG3]
{Failure isn't an option. NOW GO!}
L'échec n'est pas acceptable ! ALLEZ !

[PRI1A1]
Director: Follow the White Rabbit! You're one ugly fuckin' Alice though!

[PRI2A1]
Director: Get rid of that screw and get up to that room. The rabbit has left you a gift!

[PRI3A1]
Director: A new meaning for death row! Get yourself up to that control room!

[PRI4A1]
Director: Fine shooting! Head for the door below the control room!

[PRI5A1]
Director: Watch those cells closely! Pick them all off!

[PRI6A1]
Director: Almost there, get through this last section anyway you can!

[PRI_08]
Rabbit: You did well! Very well. Every film has an ending and this is yours.

[PRI7A1]
Director: What can I say? You were a good leading man, the audience will love you... don't expect any royalty cheques where you're going though!

[PRI_10]
White Rabbit: Shit! The punk has survived the final cut! He gets me, he gets out! Get me some backup!

[PRI_15]
Director: The rabbit is dead! Storm that tower!

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!