[GOAL1]
{Find a way into the factory complex}
Finde einen Weg in den Fabrik-Komplex.

[GOAL2]
{Use the lever in the guard hut to open the ~blue~loading bay~colour~ gates}
Öffne das Tor zum ~blue~Ladeplatz~colour~ mit dem Hebel im Wachhäuschen.

[GOAL3]
{Try to make your way to the factory's front reception area}
Schlag dich zum Empfangsbereich vorne in der Fabrik durch.

[GOAL4]
{The lift is out of action. Deactivate the failsafe to power it up again}
Der Aufzug funktioniert nicht. Deaktiviere die Ausfallsicherung, um ihn wieder einzuschalten.

[GOAL5]
{Get to the reception area and exit the factory anyway you can}
Begib dich zum Empfangsbereich und verlasse die Fabrik.

[GOAL6]
{The main doors are locked via the control room console}
Die Haupttüren wurden vom Kontrollraum aus verschlossen.

[GOAL7]
{Exit the factory complex and head for the ~blue~loading bay~colour~}
Verlasse das Fabrik-Gelände und begib dich zum ~blue~Ladeplatz~colour~.

[GRV1A1]
{Time for a little overtime! Make your way through the factory!}
Zeit für Überstunden! Bahne dir einen Weg durch die Fabrik!

[GRV1A2]
{The loading bay's your only way in.}
Du kannst nur über den Ladeplatz hineingelangen.

[GRV13A1]
{For a job well done make your way to the foyer.}
Wäre klasse, wenn du dich zum Foyer durchschlagen würdest.

[GRV2A1]
{Well that's put a spanner in the works. Why don't you try the guard hut.}
Na, das war wohl nichts. Versuch's doch mal beim Wachhäuschen.

[GRV3A1]
{Way to go, Cash! Now make your way through the factory.}
So ist's richtig, Cash! Jetzt bahn dir einen Weg durch die Fabrik.

[GRV4A1]
{Aw dammit, the lift's screwed again!}
Ach verdammt, der Aufzug ist schon wieder kaputt!

[GRV4A2]
{You're going to have to go down to the basement.}
Du wirst wohl in den Keller gehen müssen.

[GRV5A1]
{There's a circuit breaker down there that will get the lift working.}
Da unten ist der Hauptschalter. Damit kannst du den Aufzug wieder einschalten.

[GRV6A1]
{You need to reset the circuit breaker in the basement for the lift to work!}
Du musst den Hauptschalter im Keller wieder einschalten, damit der Aufzug funktioniert!

[GRV7A1]
{You need to reset the circuit breaker for the lift to work!}
Du musst den Hauptschalter wieder einschalten, damit der Aufzug funktioniert!

[GRV8A1]
{Nice one, Cash. The lift should be working now.}
Gut gemacht, Cash. Der Aufzug müsste jetzt funktionieren.

[GRV9A1]
{Ok, I admit it - some of the doors are locked via a}
O. K., ich geb's zu - einige der Türen wurden mit dem Schaltpult

[GRV9A2]
{panel in the control room - sorry.}
im Kontrollraum verschlossen - tut mir Leid.

[GRV10A1]
{That's my leading man! Attaboy! See you with some beers outside!}
Das nenn ich einen Hauptdarsteller! Sehr gut! Ich warte draußen mit einem Bierchen auf dich!

[GRV11A1]
{I told you. You're gonna have to use the panel in the control room to open the door!}
Ich hab's dir gesagt. Du musst das Schaltpult im Kontrollraum benutzen, um die Tür zu öffnen!

[GRV12A1]
{I don't think we've made too many friends - Hell, I like you, but these guys...}
Ich glaube, du hast dir nicht all zu viele Freunde gemacht - ich kann dich verdammt gut leiden, aber diese Typen da ...

[HINT2]
Director: Not that way! That would be too easy!

[DOORSS]
Director: Use the control room console to open these doors!

[FSAFE2]
Director: You need to get down to that basement and deactivate the failsafe...

[FSAFE3]
DIrector: It's preventing the gantry lift from working!

[FAILON]
Director: You need the failsafe off for the lift to work!

[FAILOFF]
Director: Good! That lift should be working now!

[FOLLOW3]
Director: That's it! Those main entrance doors are unlocked! Meet you outside!

[SEWAGEL]
Director: Some doors are locked via the main control room of the works!

[END]
Director: Well done for now! You haven't seen the last of that rabbit though!

[GOTHRU1]
Director: Time for a little overtime! Make your way through this factory!

[GOTHRU2]
Director: Use the loading bay as your entry point... If you can!

[LOADLOK]
Director: You'll need to reopen the loading bay gates! Check out the guard hut!

[LOADOPN]
Director: Excellent! Try and work your way through the factory complex...

[FOYER]
Director: Get to the foyer and pick up your wages when the job's done!

[HNTCTRL]
Director: That control room might be important!

[COMMIT]
Director: Seems your work isn't up to scratch! This reception committee looks pissed off!

[MPG1]
{What the fuck...}
Was zum Teufel ...

[MPG2]
{Get in the van now!}
Sofort rein in den Van!

[MPG3]
{Move it!}
Bewegung!

[MPG4]
{You heard the man!}
Ihr habt den Mann gehört!

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!