[PGKEY]
You have picked up the PRISON GATE KEY.

[GOAL1]
Follow the rabbit by exiting the cellblock

[GOAL2]
Kill the patrolling hunter and get up to the control room

[GOAL3]
Kill all the death row hunters

[GOAL4]
Get to the workshop anyway you can

[GOAL5]
Activate the sensor lock and chase that rabbit

[GOAL6]
Kill the ~green~White Rabbit~colour~ to acquire the KEY to the prison's gates

[GOAL7]
Get to the gates and exit the prison

[SCREW1]
Darling, I'm coming to get you!

[COVER1]
Take cover, you idiots!

[COVER2]
Take cover! Take cover!

[COVER3]
He's packing! Take cover!

[DIE1]
You did well! Very well. But every film has its ending and this here is yours!

[DIE2]
You made it! Oh dear, you see, you didn't make it after all! Ha-ha-heee-hooo!

[DIE3]
Close your eyes, bad boy! Time for bye-byes!

[OUT1]
Hey, you ain't dead! He ain't dead! Oh shit, I've got the keys outta here!

[OUT2]
You're supposed to be dead! Aw fuck, he's after my frikkin' key!

[OUT3]
Holy frogger! I've got the key - if he gets me he's outta here!

[POL1A1]
You're my big ugly Alice, so go on, follow the White Rabbit!

[POL2A1]
They're messing with you, Cash, trying to fuck with your head! I wouldn't stand for that!

[POL3A1]
You might want to clean the filth out of the showers...

[POL4A1]
Get rid of the pink dressed freak and get up to the watch room. Mr. Rabbit has left you a gift!

[POL5A1]
A new meaning for death row! Get yourself up to that watch room!

[POL6A1]
You're a threshing machine, Cash! Now head for the door below the control room!

[POL7A1]
Watch those cells closely. Kill 'em all!

[POL8A1]
Almost there, baby! Chew your way through these chumps!

[POL9A1]
What can I say? You were a good leading man, the audience will love you.

[POL9A2]
Don't expect any royalty cheques where you're going though!

[POL10A1]
Hey, Cash, what are you doing? Are you insane?

[POL11A1]
Where are you gonna go? The state wants you dead, Cash, dead!

[POL12A1]
Cash? Come back here!

[MPG1]
Ramirez!

[MPG2]
You let Cash slip his leash - bring him to heel!

[MPG3]
Failure isn't an option. NOW GO!

[PRI1A1]
Director: Follow the White Rabbit! You're one ugly fuckin' Alice though!

[PRI2A1]
Director: Get rid of that screw and get up to that room. The rabbit has left you a gift!

[PRI3A1]
Director: A new meaning for death row! Get yourself up to that control room!

[PRI4A1]
Director: Fine shooting! Head for the door below the control room!

[PRI5A1]
Director: Watch those cells closely! Pick them all off!

[PRI6A1]
Director: Almost there, get through this last section anyway you can!

[PRI_08]
Rabbit: You did well! Very well. Every film has an ending and this is yours.

[PRI7A1]
Director: What can I say? You were a good leading man, the audience will love you... don't expect any royalty cheques where you're going though!

[PRI_10]
White Rabbit: Shit! The punk has survived the final cut! He gets me, he gets out! Get me some backup!

[PRI_15]
Director: The rabbit is dead! Storm that tower!

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!