[GOAL1]
Find a way into the factory complex

[GOAL2]
Use the lever in the guard hut to open the ~blue~loading bay~colour~ gates

[GOAL3]
Try to make your way to the factory's front reception area

[GOAL4]
The lift is out of action. Deactivate the failsafe to power it up again

[GOAL5]
Get to the reception area and exit the factory anyway you can

[GOAL6]
The main doors are locked via the control room console

[GOAL7]
Exit the factory complex and head for the ~blue~loading bay~colour~

[GRV1A1]
Time for a little overtime! Make your way through the factory!

[GRV1A2]
The loading bay's your only way in.

[GRV13A1]
For a job well done make your way to the foyer.

[GRV2A1]
Well that's put a spanner in the works. Why don't you try the guard hut.

[GRV3A1]
Way to go, Cash! Now make your way through the factory.

[GRV4A1]
Aw dammit, the lift's screwed again!

[GRV4A2]
You're going to have to go down to the basement.

[GRV5A1]
There's a circuit breaker down there that will get the lift working.

[GRV6A1]
You need to reset the circuit breaker in the basement for the lift to work!

[GRV7A1]
You need to reset the circuit breaker for the lift to work!

[GRV8A1]
Nice one, Cash. The lift should be working now.

[GRV9A1]
Ok, I admit it - some of the doors are locked via a

[GRV9A2]
panel in the control room - sorry.

[GRV10A1]
That's my leading man! Attaboy! See you with some beers outside!

[GRV11A1]
I told you. You're gonna have to use the panel in the control room to open the door!

[GRV12A1]
I don't think we've made too many friends - Hell, I like you, but these guys...

[MPG1]
What the fuck...

[MPG2]
Get in the van now!

[MPG3]
Move it!

[MPG4]
You heard the man!

[HINT2]
Director: Not that way! That would be too easy!

[DOORSS]
Director: Use the control room console to open these doors!

[FSAFE2]
Director: You need to get down to that basement and deactivate the failsafe...

[FSAFE3]
DIrector: It's preventing the gantry lift from working!

[FAILON]
Director: You need the failsafe off for the lift to work!

[FAILOFF]
Director: Good! That lift should be working now!

[FOLLOW3]
Director: That's it! Those main entrance doors are unlocked! Meet you outside!

[SEWAGEL]
Director: Some doors are locked via the main control room of the works!

[END]
Director: Well done for now! You haven't seen the last of that rabbit though!

[GOTHRU1]
Director: Time for a little overtime! Make your way through this factory!

[GOTHRU2]
Director: Use the loading bay as your entry point... If you can!

[LOADLOK]
Director: You'll need to reopen the loading bay gates! Check out the guard hut!

[LOADOPN]
Director: Excellent! Try and work your way through the factory complex...

[FOYER]
Director: Get to the foyer and pick up your wages when the job's done!

[HNTCTRL]
Director: That control room might be important!

[COMMIT]
Director: Seems your work isn't up to scratch! This reception committee looks pissed off!

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!