[GOAL1]
{Find a way into the factory complex}
Descubre cómo entrar en el complejo industrial.

[GOAL2]
{Use the lever in the guard hut to open the ~blue~loading bay~colour~ gates}
Utiliza la palanca de la garita de la guardia para abrir las puertas del ~blue~compartimiento de carga~colour~.

[GOAL3]
{Try to make your way to the factory's front reception area}
Intenta abrirte paso hasta la zona de la entrada principal de la fábrica.

[GOAL4]
{The lift is out of action. Deactivate the failsafe to power it up again}
El ascensor no funciona. Desactiva los sistemas de seguridad para que vuelva a tener energía.

[GOAL5]
{Get to the reception area and exit the factory anyway you can}
Ve a la entrada principal y sal de la fábrica por donde puedas.

[GOAL6]
{The main doors are locked via the control room console}
Las puertas principales están cerradas mediante la consola de la sala de control.

[GOAL7]
{Exit the factory complex and head for the ~blue~loading bay~colour~}
Sal del complejo industrial y dirígete al ~blue~compartimiento de carga~colour~.

[GRV1A1]
{Time for a little overtime! Make your way through the factory!}
¡Hay que hacer horas extras! ¡Ábrete camino por la fábrica!

[GRV1A2]
{The loading bay's your only way in.}
La única forma de entrar es por el compartimiento de carga.

[GRV13A1]
{For a job well done make your way to the foyer.}
Si quieres un trabajo bien hecho, ve hasta el vestíbulo.

[GRV2A1]
{Well that's put a spanner in the works. Why don't you try the guard hut.}
Bueno, eso es como meter un palo entre los radios de una rueda. ¿Por qué no pruebas en la garita de la guardia?

[GRV3A1]
{Way to go, Cash! Now make your way through the factory.}
¡Sigue así, Cash! Ahora ábrete camino por la fábrica...

[GRV4A1]
{Aw dammit, the lift's screwed again!}
¡Maldita sea! ¡El ascensor ha vuelto a petar!

[GRV4A2]
{You're going to have to go down to the basement.}
Tendrás que bajar hasta el sótano.

[GRV5A1]
{There's a circuit breaker down there that will get the lift working.}
Allí hay un disyuntor que hará que el ascensor funcione.

[GRV6A1]
{You need to reset the circuit breaker in the basement for the lift to work!}
¡Para que funcione el ascensor, tendrás que reiniciar el disyuntor del sótano!

[GRV7A1]
{You need to reset the circuit breaker for the lift to work!}
¡Para que funcione el ascensor, tendrás que reiniciar el disyuntor!

[GRV8A1]
{Nice one, Cash. The lift should be working now.}
Bien hecho, Cash. Ahora el ascensor debería funcionar.

[GRV9A1]
{Ok, I admit it - some of the doors are locked via a}
Bueno, lo admito, algunas de las puertas están cerradas

[GRV9A2]
{panel in the control room - sorry.}
desde un panel en la sala de control, lo siento.

[GRV10A1]
{That's my leading man! Attaboy! See you with some beers outside!}
¡Ése es mi protagonista! ¡Muy bien hecho! ¡Nos tomaremos unas birras cuando estés fuera!

[GRV11A1]
{I told you. You're gonna have to use the panel in the control room to open the door!}
Te lo dije. ¡Para abrir la puerta tendrás que usar el panel de la sala de control!

[GRV12A1]
{I don't think we've made too many friends - Hell, I like you, but these guys...}
No creo que hayas hecho muchos amigos; joder, a mí me caes bien, pero a estos tíos...

[HINT2]
Director: Not that way! That would be too easy!

[DOORSS]
Director: Use the control room console to open these doors!

[FSAFE2]
Director: You need to get down to that basement and deactivate the failsafe...

[FSAFE3]
DIrector: It's preventing the gantry lift from working!

[FAILON]
Director: You need the failsafe off for the lift to work!

[FAILOFF]
Director: Good! That lift should be working now!

[FOLLOW3]
Director: That's it! Those main entrance doors are unlocked! Meet you outside!

[SEWAGEL]
Director: Some doors are locked via the main control room of the works!

[END]
Director: Well done for now! You haven't seen the last of that rabbit though!

[GOTHRU1]
Director: Time for a little overtime! Make your way through this factory!

[GOTHRU2]
Director: Use the loading bay as your entry point... If you can!

[LOADLOK]
Director: You'll need to reopen the loading bay gates! Check out the guard hut!

[LOADOPN]
Director: Excellent! Try and work your way through the factory complex...

[FOYER]
Director: Get to the foyer and pick up your wages when the job's done!

[HNTCTRL]
Director: That control room might be important!

[COMMIT]
Director: Seems your work isn't up to scratch! This reception committee looks pissed off!

[MPG1]
{What the fuck...}
Qué cojones...

[MPG2]
{Get in the van now!}
¡Entra en la furgoneta de una vez!

[MPG3]
{Move it!}
¡Mueve el culo!

[MPG4]
{You heard the man!}
¡Ya lo has oído!

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!