[GOAL1]
{Find a way into the factory complex}
Trouve un accès à l'usine.

[GOAL2]
{Use the lever in the guard hut to open the ~blue~loading bay~colour~ gates}
Utilise le levier de la guérite pour ouvrir les ~blue~portes de chargement~colour~.

[GOAL3]
{Try to make your way to the factory's front reception area}
Fraie-toi un chemin jusqu'à l'accueil de l'usine.

[GOAL4]
{The lift is out of action. Deactivate the failsafe to power it up again}
L'ascenseur est HS. Désactive la sécurité pour rétablir le courant.

[GOAL5]
{Get to the reception area and exit the factory anyway you can}
Va jusqu'à l'accueil et démerde-toi pour sortir de l'usine.

[GOAL6]
{The main doors are locked via the control room console}
Les portes principales sont verrouillées par la console de la salle de contrôle.

[GOAL7]
{Exit the factory complex and head for the ~blue~loading bay~colour~}
Sors de l'usine et dirige-toi vers les ~blue~portes de chargement~colour~. }

[GRV1A1]
{Time for a little overtime! Make your way through the factory!}
Va falloir faire des heures sup' ! Traverse l'usine !

[GRV1A2]
{The loading bay's your only way in.}
Y'a qu'une entrée : les portes de chargement.

[GRV13A1]
{For a job well done make your way to the foyer.}
Pour bien faire ton boulot, va jusqu'au hall d'entrée.

[GRV2A1]
{Well that's put a spanner in the works. Why don't you try the guard hut.}
C'est ce que j'appelle un grain de sable dans un engrenage. Essaie donc la guérite.

[GRV3A1]
{Way to go, Cash! Now make your way through the factory.}
Bravo, Cash ! Maintenant traverse l'usine !

[GRV4A1]
{Aw dammit, the lift's screwed again!}
Et merde, l'ascenseur est encore bloqué !

[GRV4A2]
{You're going to have to go down to the basement.}
Tu vas devoir descendre au sous-sol.

[GRV5A1]
{There's a circuit breaker down there that will get the lift working.}
Il y a un disjoncteur qui rétablira le courant dans l'ascenseur.

[GRV6A1]
{You need to reset the circuit breaker in the basement for the lift to work!}
Faut actionner le disjoncteur du sous-sol pour faire marcher l'ascenseur !

[GRV7A1]
{You need to reset the circuit breaker for the lift to work!}
Faut actionner le disjoncteur pour faire marcher l'ascenseur.

[GRV8A1]
{Nice one, Cash. The lift should be working now.}
Joli, Cash ! L'ascenseur doit marcher, maintenant.

[GRV9A1]
{Ok, I admit it - some of the doors are locked via a}
OK, j'avoue. Certaines portes sont verrouillées par

[GRV9A2]
{panel in the control room - sorry.}
une console de la salle de contrôle. Désolé.

[GRV10A1]
{That's my leading man! Attaboy! See you with some beers outside!}
Ca, c'est du beau boulot ! Bravo, petit ! Je te paierai un coup !

[GRV11A1]
{I told you. You're gonna have to use the panel in the control room to open the door!}
Je te l'ai déjà dit. Faut utiliser la console de la salle de contrôle pour ouvrir la porte !

[GRV12A1]
{I don't think we've made too many friends - Hell, I like you, but these guys...}
Tu t'es pas fait des copains, on dirait. Moi, je t'aime bien, par contre ces gars-là...

[MPG1]
{What the fuck...}
Putain, mais qu'est-ce que...

[MPG2]
{Get in the van now!}
Monte dans le van maintenant !

[MPG3]
{Move it!}
Plus vite !

[MPG4]
{You heard the man!}
Tu l'as entendu !

[HINT2]
Director: Not that way! That would be too easy!

[DOORSS]
Director: Use the control room console to open these doors!

[FSAFE2]
Director: You need to get down to that basement and deactivate the failsafe...

[FSAFE3]
DIrector: It's preventing the gantry lift from working!

[FAILON]
Director: You need the failsafe off for the lift to work!

[FAILOFF]
Director: Good! That lift should be working now!

[FOLLOW3]
Director: That's it! Those main entrance doors are unlocked! Meet you outside!

[SEWAGEL]
Director: Some doors are locked via the main control room of the works!

[END]
Director: Well done for now! You haven't seen the last of that rabbit though!

[GOTHRU1]
Director: Time for a little overtime! Make your way through this factory!

[GOTHRU2]
Director: Use the loading bay as your entry point... If you can!

[LOADLOK]
Director: You'll need to reopen the loading bay gates! Check out the guard hut!

[LOADOPN]
Director: Excellent! Try and work your way through the factory complex...

[FOYER]
Director: Get to the foyer and pick up your wages when the job's done!

[HNTCTRL]
Director: That control room might be important!

[COMMIT]
Director: Seems your work isn't up to scratch! This reception committee looks pissed off!

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!