[GOAL1]
{Find a way into the factory complex}
Trova il modo di raggiungere il complesso industriale.

[GOAL2]
{Use the lever in the guard hut to open the ~blue~loading bay~colour~ gates}
Usa la leva nella guardiola per aprire i cancelli della ~blue~zona di carico~colour~.

[GOAL3]
{Try to make your way to the factory's front reception area}
Trova il modo di raggiungere la portineria della fabbrica.

[GOAL4]
{The lift is out of action. Deactivate the failsafe to power it up again}
L'ascensore è fuori servizio. Disattiva il dispositivo di arresto di sicurezza.

[GOAL5]
{Get to the reception area and exit the factory anyway you can}
Raggiungi la portineria ed esci dalla fabbrica.

[GOAL6]
{The main doors are locked via the control room console}
L'ingresso principale è chiuso con un pannello della sala di controllo.

[GOAL7]
{Exit the factory complex and head for the ~blue~loading bay~colour~}
Esci dal complesso industriale e dirigiti verso la ~blue~zona di carico~colour~.

[MPG1]
{What the fuck...}
Cosa diavolo...?

[MPG2]
{Get in the van now!}
Infilati nel furgone!

[MPG3]
{Move it!}
Muoviti!

[MPG4]
{You heard the man!}
Non ci senti!?!

[GRV1A1]
{Time for a little overtime! Make your way through the factory!}
È ora di un po' di straordinari! Entra in fabbrica!

[GRV1A2]
{The loading bay's your only way in.}
La zona di carico è l'unico modo che hai per accedervi.

[GRV13A1]
{For a job well done make your way to the foyer.}
Per fare un buon lavoro, raggiungi l'atrio.

[GRV2A1]
{Well that's put a spanner in the works. Why don't you try the guard hut.}
Ti vedo un po' smarrito. Perché non provi nella guardiola?

[GRV3A1]
{Way to go, Cash! Now make your way through the factory.}
Via libera, Cash! Adesso entra nella fabbrica...

[GRV4A1]
{Aw dammit, the lift's screwed again!}
Dannazione, l'ascensore è ancora fuori uso!

[GRV4A2]
{You're going to have to go down to the basement.}
Dovrai scendere nello scantinato.

[GRV5A1]
{There's a circuit breaker down there that will get the lift working.}
Lì c'è un generatore che farà funzionare l'ascensore.

[GRV6A1]
{You need to reset the circuit breaker in the basement for the lift to work!}
Devi riattivare il generatore nello scantinato per far funzionare l'ascensore!

[GRV7A1]
{You need to reset the circuit breaker for the lift to work!}
Devi riattivare il generatore per far funzionare l'ascensore!

[GRV8A1]
{Nice one, Cash. The lift should be working now.}
Ben fatto, Cash. Ora l'ascensore dovrebbe funzionare.

[GRV9A1]
{Ok, I admit it - some of the doors are locked via a}
Ok, lo ammetto... alcune porte sono chiuse con un

[GRV9A2]
{panel in the control room - sorry.}
pannello nella sala di controllo... mi spiace.

[GRV10A1]
{That's my leading man! Attaboy! See you with some beers outside!}
Ecco il mio protagonista! Bravo! Ci vediamo fuori con un paio di birre!

[GRV11A1]
{I told you. You're gonna have to use the panel in the control room to open the door!}
Te l'ho detto. Devi usare il pannello nella sala di controllo per aprire la porta!

[GRV12A1]
{I don't think we've made too many friends - Hell, I like you, but these guys...}
Non credo che ti sia fatto molti amici... Dannazione, mi piaci, ma questi ragazzi...

[HINT2]
Director: Not that way! That would be too easy!

[DOORSS]
Director: Use the control room console to open these doors!

[FSAFE2]
Director: You need to get down to that basement and deactivate the failsafe...

[FSAFE3]
DIrector: It's preventing the gantry lift from working!

[FAILON]
Director: You need the failsafe off for the lift to work!

[FAILOFF]
Director: Good! That lift should be working now!

[FOLLOW3]
Director: That's it! Those main entrance doors are unlocked! Meet you outside!

[SEWAGEL]
Director: Some doors are locked via the main control room of the works!

[END]
Director: Well done for now! You haven't seen the last of that rabbit though!

[GOTHRU1]
Director: Time for a little overtime! Make your way through this factory!

[GOTHRU2]
Director: Use the loading bay as your entry point... If you can!

[LOADLOK]
Director: You'll need to reopen the loading bay gates! Check out the guard hut!

[LOADOPN]
Director: Excellent! Try and work your way through the factory complex...

[FOYER]
Director: Get to the foyer and pick up your wages when the job's done!

[HNTCTRL]
Director: That control room might be important!

[COMMIT]
Director: Seems your work isn't up to scratch! This reception committee looks pissed off!

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!