[GOD1]
Kill ~green~Ramirez~colour~ before he calls in back up!

[GOD2]
Make your way to the ~blue~gate~colour~!

[GOAL1]
Dispose of the three stalking hunters

[GOAL2]
Get into the old apartment block and track down ~green~Ramirez~colour~

[GOAL3]
Kill ~green~Ramirez~colour~ before he calls in back up

[GOAL4]
Make your way to the ~blue~gate~colour~

[GOAL5]
Kill ~green~Ramirez~colour~

[KILL1]
Get out there and bring me his fucking head!

[KILL2]
He's making fools of us - get out there and find him!

[KILL3]
First man brings me his severed dick gets ten thousand dollars!

[SRCH1]
Move it, you assholes, he's down there somewhere!

[SRCH2]
You inept motherfuckers! He's down there - Find him!

[SRCH3]
He's making fools of you all! Check the shadows!

[SRCH4]
Put some fucking effort into it!

[SRCH5]
Look harder, you spineless gimps!

[SRCH6]
He's laughing at you! Assholes!

[SRCH7]
This isn't a game! Find him!

[SRCH8]
If you don't find him soon I'll shoot you myself!

[SRCH9]
I swear I'll kill you all myself if you don't find that motherfucker soon!

[SRCH10]
He's here somewhere! Just flush him out so I can nail the bastard!

[MPG0]
Where do you think you're going, little man? Huh? Huh!

[MPG1]
You think you're tough?

[MPG2]
Think you're tough?

[MPG3]
I'll rip your fucking head off!

[MPG4]
You like hide and seek? You like hide and fucking seek?

[MPG5]
Well we're coming for you, asshole.

[MPG24]
What the fuck?

[MPG25]
Don't you want to play any more?

[MPG26]
What's the matter, little boy?

[MPG27]
It's our turn now! Run, RUN!

[MPG28]
Ready or not  HA HA!

[MPG6]
Get in, you idiot, GET IN!

[MPG7]
THERE HE IS!!

[MPG8]
Pull over - PULL OVER!

[MPG9]
Who are you - I've seen your face before!

[MPG10]
Get offa me! I'm a reporter - I was at your execution!

[MPG11]
Keep talking.

[MPG12]
I've been following Starkweather's little operation for months.

[MPG13]
Who's Starkweather?

[MPG14]
The guy that's been talking you through this whole circus of death!

[MPG15]
Look, I've got all I need to expose that sick bastard

[MPG16]
But he's definitely onto me now, so I have to get back to my apartment

[MPG17]
Collect my material and get out of town before I become another of Starkweather's 'extras'.

[MPG19]
You can bring him down, this Starkweather?

[MPG20]
Absolutely - this is gonna make my career.

[MPG21]
Ok, let's go.

[MPG22]
Huh?

[MPG23]
To your apartment  DRIVE!

[RAMINTR]
Ramirez: Flush that bitch-ass punk out! I'm da black Lee Harvey Oswald!

[RAMKILL]
Ramirez: He gives you any trouble, slice that punk into food for my bitch!

[RAMGUN]
Ramirez: Bitch! Unlock that bottom door! He gets to me, he really is a bad ass!

[RAMHERE]
Ramirez: How'd he get this far? I gotta do tha job myself!

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!