[NAIL]
{When using guns, shoot by pressing the Action button.}
Quando usi le pistole, spara premendo il tasto Azione.

[NAIL2]
{Press the Action2 button to zoom in on the closest hunter.}
Premi il tasto Azione2 per zoomare verso i cacciatori.

[NAIL0]
{When wall-strafing you can aim at hunters around corners by holding the Action2 button.}
Quando strisci contro un muro, puoi mirare i cacciatori oltre l'angolo tenendo premuto il tasto Azione2.

[NAIL1]
{Press the Reload button to reload your weapon.}
Premi il tasto Ricarica per ricaricare l'arma.

[NAIL4]
{Press the Reload button to reload your weapon.}
Premi il tasto Ricarica per ricaricare l'arma.

[NAIL3]
{Aim to the head if you can. Headshots do more damage and with firearms they can kill instantly.}
Se ne hai la possibilità, mira alla testa. I colpi alla testa provocano maggiori danni e, se effettuati con armi da fuoco, uccidono istantaneamente.

[PADLOCK]
{You need something sharp to cut this rope.}
Hai bisogno di qualcosa di affilato per tagliare la corda.

[OPEN]
{Kill that hunter to open this gate.}
Uccidi il cacciatore per aprire questo cancello.

[DRUM]
{You can detonate these Gas Canisters by shooting them with the nailgun.}
Puoi far detonare queste bombe fumogene sparandogli contro con la sparachiodi.

[AMMOPK]
{This is an ammo pick-up, you must have the desired weapon in your inventory to collect this.}
Puoi raccogliere queste munizioni solo se hai l'arma adatta nel tuo inventario.

[GOAL1]
{Kill the hunter guarding the gate}
Uccidi il cacciatore di guardia al cancello.

[GOAL2]
{Find something to cut the ~blue~rope ~colour~on the gate}
Trova qualcosa per tagliare la ~blue~corda ~colour~sul cancello.

[GOAL3]
{Find a way into the trailer to get the nailgun}
Entra nel rimorchio e recupera lo sparachiodi.

[GOAL4]
{Find and activate the switch to open the ~blue~gate}
Trova e aziona l'interruttore per aprire il ~blue~cancello~colour~.

[GOAL5]
{Go back to the gate to get to the exit}
Per raggiungere l'uscita, torna al cancello.

[CRAP1]
{I can smell it's putrid corruption}
Questa è sporca corruzione.

[CRAP2]
{Hallelujah! Praise The Lord!}
Alleluia! Sia lodato il cielo!

[WHO1]
{Hallelujah! There he is!}
Alleluia! Eccolo!

[WHO2]
{Hallelujah! There he is!}
Alleluia! Eccolo!

[FILL1]
{There he is! Sick deviant...}
Eccolo! Maledetto pervertito...

[FILL2]
{The Lord hath delivered! Amen!}
Riposi in pace! Amen!

[SEEN1]
{G-guys! I... I see him! He's here! Guys!}
R...ragazzi! L...lo vedo! È qui! Ragazzi!

[SEEN2]
{Holy fuck - th - there he is! Hey he's over here!}
Santo cielo... ec...eccolo! Ehi, è qui!

[WHT1A1]
{Ok, so I lied. We haven't quite wrapped this gig up, but hey}
Ok, ho mentito. Non è ancora arrivato il momento di calare il sipario, ma...

[WHT1A2]
{you're having fun, right?!}
...almeno ti stai divertendo, vero?

[WHT1A3]
{There's a double gate that leads on through to our next location - find it.}
C'è un doppio cancello che porta al tuo prossimo set... trovalo.

[WHT2A1]
{Careful, there's a bigot guarding the gate. If he sees you he'll call his cheery buddies...}
Fai attenzione, c'è un disgraziato di guardia al cancello. Se ti vede, chiamerà i suoi simpatici amici...

[WHT3A1]
{That's a pretty thick rope - you're gonna need a blade...}
È una corda piuttosto spessa... ti servirà una lama...

[WHT4A1]
{You didn't think I'd let you out that easily did you? It's an electric lock}
Pensavi che ti avrei lasciato andare così facilmente, vero? È una serratura elettronica.

[WHT4A2]
{Find the release switch.}
Trova il comando di apertura.

[WHT5A1]
{Beautiful! That's his hunting days over!}
Perfetto! Quel dannato cacciatore è passato a miglior vita!

[WHT6A1]
{There's a nailgun in that trailer - if you can stand the smell!}
C'è una sparachiodi nel rimorchio, se riesci a sopportare il fetore!

[WHT7A1]
{He's got his hands full at the moment - go grab his nailgun...}
In questo momento ha le mani occupate. Vai a prendere lo sparachiodi.

[MPG1]
{Ok, you limp-dicked faggots!}
Luridi smidollati!

[MPG2]
{Let's give Mr. Starkweather a show to remember.}
Prepariamo uno spettacolo indimenticabile per Mr. Starkweather!

[MPG3]
{MOVE IT!!}
FORZA!!!

[INTRO]
Director : Find this gate, and get past it.

[WATCH]
Director : Watch out for this guy though, he'll call in back-up if he sees you.

[START]
Director : Your on the Skinz turf now Cash, these racist pricks hate everything, grab a weapon and find a way into the scrapyard.

[GLASS]
Hunter : Bastard, You made me shit my pants.

[GATE]
Spotter : I see him, I see him, calling in back-up.

[EXIT]
Director : Through that door is the way out, I've hidden a power switch to open it, find that switch.

[DOPE]
Director : If you could just find a way into the trailer and steal that nailgun....

[HEAR]
Hunter : Is that you guys out there?, comon I'm taking a crap in here.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!