[GAS]
{Pick up the gas can with the Use button and take it back to the crane.}
Raccogli la tanica di benzina con il tasto Usa e riportala alla gru.

[CRANE]
{To rotate the crane use the keyboard or the mouse. To activate the magnet press the Action button.}
Puoi ruotare la gru usando la tastiera o il mouse. Per attivare il magnete premi il tasto Azione.

[CRANE1]
{You can leave the crane by pressing the Use button.}
Puoi lasciare la gru premendo il tasto Usa.

[CRANE2]
{Be careful as hunters can still shoot you whilst inside the crane.}
Stai attento, i cacciatori possono spararti mentre sei sulla gru.

[ENTER]
{To enter the crane stand on the ground beside it and press the Use button.}
Per salire sulla gru, posizionati accanto a essa e premi il tasto Usa.

[SQUASH]
{You can squash hunters by dropping the fridge on them using the Action button.}
Puoi schiacciare i cacciatori facendo cadere loro addosso il frigorifero con il tasto Azione.

[FUEL]
{Take the gas can up the steps and press the Use button to refuel the crane.}
Solleva la tanica di benzina e premi il tasto Usa per rifornire la gru.

[OUT]
{Find some gas to get the crane working.}
Trova della benzina per far funzionare la gru.

[ON]
{You need some gas to activate this crane.}
Hai bisogno di carburante per far funzionare la gru.

[GREEN]
{Your next objective is shown on the radar as a green dot.}
Il tuo prossimo obiettivo è indicato dal puntino verde sul radar.

[GOAL1]
{Clear the area of hunters to open the ~blue~gate}
Per aprire il ~blue~cancello~colour~, ripulisci l'area dai cacciatori.

[GOAL2]
{Find a way to lure out the hunter}
Trova un modo per attirare il cacciatore.

[GOAL3]
{Find the gasoline to fill the crane}
Trova la benzina per rifornire la gru.

[GOAL4]
{Head back with the gasoline to refuel the crane}
Torna indietro con la benzina per rifornire la gru.

[GOAL5]
{Use the crane to unblock the path}
Usa la gru per liberare la strada.

[GOAL5A]
{Find the crusher machine}
Trova la pressa.

[GOAL6]
{Hunt down the five hunters to open the ~blue~gate}
Abbatti cinque cacciatori per aprire il ~blue~cancello~colour~.

[GOAL7]
{Use the crane to unblock the path}
Usa la gru per liberare la strada.

[GOAL8]
{Find the double doors to get to the exit}
Trova le doppie porte per raggiungere l'uscita.

[GOAL9]
{Find a way to the hut}
Raggiungi la baracca.

[BLOCK1]
{Cover the fuckin exits! Now!}
Copriamo quella fottuta uscita!

[BLOCK2]
{Don't let him outta here! Move it, move it!}
Non facciamolo uscire! Muoviamoci, muoviamoci!

[FUSE1]
{What the - ? How many god damned times can a fuse blow?!}
Cosa...? Quante cazzo di volte può bruciare un fusibile?!?

[FUSE2]
{Aw that's just frickin' great - the fuse has fried again!}
È stato semplicemente grandioso... il fusibile è partito di nuovo!

[SKN1A1]
{These Skinz are boring me - dumb-assed supremacist bastards.}
Questi Skinz mi stanno davvero scocciando... dannati bastardi all'ennesima potenza.

[SKN1A2]
{Always blaming others for their inadequacies.}
Sempre a incolpare gli altri per la loro incapacità.

[SKN1A3]
{Butcher them, Cash. Cut'em up, beat 'em down and choke the fucking life out of them!}
Falli a pezzi, Cash. Triturali, maciullali, affettali e spremili come dei limoni!

[SKN2A1]
{Oh, man, that one was good! The gate's open.}
Ci è andata bene! Il cancello è aperto.

[SKN2A2]
{Go on, get out of here!}
Avanti, esci subito di qui!

[SKN3A1]
{This shit seems content to watch porn and avoid all the action! If he won't switch it off himself,}
Come si fa a restare incollati davanti a un porno e perdersi tutta l'azione! Se proprio non vogliono spegnere la TV,

[SKN3A2]
{we'll have to do it for him!}
credo che dovrai pensarci tu!

[SKN4A1]
{A crane. Well what d'ya reckon, Cash?}
Una gru. Cosa ne pensi, Cash?!?

[SKN5A1]
{Alright Cash, Grab the blade you're gonna need it to get out of here.}
D'accordo, Cash, afferra la lama che ti servirà per uscire da qui.

[SKN6A1]
{You'll need to find a way through the next gate.}
Devi trovare il modo di superare il prossimo cancello.

[SKN7A1]
{Find a way to get that fat bastard out into the open!}
Trova il modo per far uscire allo scoperto quel fottuto grassone!

[SKN8A1]
{Excellent - Death by heavy domestic appliance!}
Grandioso... Morte da abuso d'elettrodomestico!

[START]
Director : Clean the area of hunters, then make your way to the gate.

[OPEN]
Director : Nice going Cash!, The door is open.

[GASO]
Director : A busted up crane, could have some use, if you could get it working.

[DONE]
Director : Nice going Cash, scout out the area, the gates open.

[DELAY]
Hunter : That fucking fuse again, do I look like an electrician.

[HUT]
Director : You need to find a way past this gate, Cash.

[HUT1]
Director : If you could lure this fat fucker out somehow...

[ENTRY]
Hunter : Block all the exits, the only way outta here is in a body bag.

[GETTH]
{Hunter : Hey you! Get the fuck outta that crane.}
Hunter : Hey you!, get the fuck outta that crane.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!