[GAS]
{Pick up the gas can with the Use button and take it back to the crane.}
Recoge la lata de gasolina con el botón Usar y llévala a la grúa.

[CRANE]
{To rotate the crane use the keyboard or the mouse. To activate the magnet press the Action button.}
Puedes girar la grúa con el teclado o el ratón. Para activar el imán, pulsa el botón Acción.

[CRANE1]
{You can leave the crane by pressing the Use button.}
Puedes dejar la grúa pulsando el botón Usar.

[CRANE2]
{Be careful as hunters can still shoot you whilst inside the crane.}
Ten cuidado, los cazadores pueden dispararte incluso mientras estás dentro de la grúa.

[ENTER]
{To enter the crane stand on the ground beside it and press the Use button.}
Para entrar en la grúa, ponte de pie al lado de ella y pulsa el botón Usar.

[SQUASH]
{You can squash hunters by dropping the fridge on them using the Action button.}
Puedes aplastar a los cazadores dejando caer el frigorífico encima de ellos, con el botón Acción.

[FUEL]
{Take the gas can up the steps and press the Use button to refuel the crane.}
Recoge la lata de gasolina y pulsa el botón Usar para poner combustible en la grúa.

[OUT]
{Find some gas to get the crane working.}
Encuentra gasolina para que funcione la grúa.

[ON]
{You need some gas to activate this crane.}
Para arrancar la grúa, necesitas combustible.

[GREEN]
{Your next objective is shown on the radar as a green dot.}
Tu siguiente objetivo se muestra en el radar, mediante un punto verde.

[GOAL1]
{Clear the area of hunters to open the ~blue~gate}
Acaba con los cazadores de la zona para abrir la ~blue~puerta~colour~

[GOAL2]
{Find a way to lure out the hunter}
Encuentra la forma de atraer al cazador

[GOAL3]
{Find the gasoline to fill the crane}
Encuentra gasolina para llenar el depósito de la grúa

[GOAL4]
{Head back with the gasoline to refuel the crane}
Vuelve con gasolina para llenar el depósito de la grúa

[GOAL5]
{Use the crane to unblock the path}
Usa la grúa para desbloquear el camino

[GOAL5A]
{Find the crusher machine}
Encuentra la prensa de coches

[GOAL6]
{Hunt down the five hunters to open the ~blue~gate}
Para abrir la ~blue~puerta~colour~, da caza a los cinco cazadores

[GOAL7]
{Use the crane to unblock the path}
Usa la grúa para desbloquear el camino

[GOAL8]
{Find the double doors to get to the exit}
Encuentra las puertas dobles para llegar hasta la salida

[GOAL9]
{Find a way to the hut}
Encuentra un camino hasta la cabaña

[BLOCK1]
{Cover the fuckin exits! Now!}
¡Cubrid las jodidas salidas! ¡Ya!

[BLOCK2]
{Don't let him outta here! Move it, move it!}
¡Que no salga de aquí! ¡Moveos, moved el culo!

[FUSE1]
{What the - ? How many god damned times can a fuse blow?!}
¿Pero qué? ¡¿Cuántas jodidas veces puede petar un fusible?!

[FUSE2]
{Aw that's just frickin' great - the fuse has fried again!}
Ah, cojonudo, ¡el fusible ha vuelto a fallar!

[SKN1A1]
{These Skinz are boring me - dumb-assed supremacist bastards.}
Estos Skinz me aburren, estúpidos bastardos supremacistas.

[SKN1A2]
{Always blaming others for their inadequacies.}
Siempre echando la culpa a otros por su ineptitud.

[SKN1A3]
{Butcher them, Cash. Cut'em up, beat 'em down and choke the fucking life out of them!}
Machácalos, Cash. Córtalos, zúmbales ¡y estrangúlales hasta exprimirles la última gota de su patética vida!

[SKN2A1]
{Oh, man, that one was good! The gate's open.}
Tío, ¡ése era bueno! La puerta está abierta.

[SKN2A2]
{Go on, get out of here!}
Vamos, ¡salgamos de aquí!

[SKN3A1]
{This shit seems content to watch porn and avoid all the action! If he won't switch it off himself,}
¡Este mierda está contento con ver porno y escaquearse de la acción! Si no lo va a apagar él,

[SKN3A2]
{we'll have to do it for him!}
¡tendremos que hacerlo nosotros!

[SKN4A1]
{A crane. Well what d'ya reckon, Cash?}
Una grúa. Bueno, ¿qué estás pensando, Cash?

[SKN5A1]
{Alright Cash, Grab the blade you're gonna need it to get out of here.}
De acuerdo, Cash, coge el cuchillo, te hará falta par salir de aquí.

[SKN6A1]
{You'll need to find a way through the next gate.}
Tendrás que encontrar una manera de cruzar la siguiente puerta.

[SKN7A1]
{Find a way to get that fat bastard out into the open!}
¡Encuentra la forma de que ese maldito bastardo salga a campo abierto!

[SKN8A1]
{Excellent - Death by heavy domestic appliance!}
Excelente, ¡muerte por uso masivo de electrodomésticos!

[START]
Director : Clean the area of hunters, then make your way to the gate.

[OPEN]
Director : Nice going Cash!, The door is open.

[GASO]
Director : A busted up crane, could have some use, if you could get it working.

[DONE]
Director : Nice going Cash, scout out the area, the gates open.

[DELAY]
Hunter : That fucking fuse again, do I look like an electrician.

[HUT]
Director : You need to find a way past this gate, Cash.

[HUT1]
Director : If you could lure this fat fucker out somehow...

[ENTRY]
Hunter : Block all the exits, the only way outta here is in a body bag.

[GETTH]
{Hunter : Hey you! Get the fuck outta that crane.}
Hunter : Hey you!, get the fuck outta that crane.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!