[LETTER1]
abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ 0123456789"$,.'-?!!SDBF

[NUMBER1]
0123456789

[GAS]
Pick up the gas can with the Use button and take it back to the crane.

[CRANE]
To rotate the crane use the keyboard or the mouse. To activate the magnet press the Action button.

[CRANE1]
You can leave the crane by pressing the Use button.

[CRANE2]
Be careful as hunters can still shoot you whilst inside the crane.

[ENTER]
To enter the crane stand on the ground beside it and press the Use button.

[SQUASH]
You can squash hunters by dropping the fridge on them using the Action button.

[FUEL]
Take the gas can up the steps and press the Use button to refuel the crane.

[OUT]
Find some gas to get the crane working.

[ON]
You need some gas to activate this crane.

[GREEN]
Your next objective is shown on the radar as a green dot.

[GOAL1]
Clear the area of hunters to open the ~blue~gate

[GOAL2]
Find a way to lure out the hunter

[GOAL3]
Find the gasoline to fill the crane

[GOAL4]
Head back with the gasoline to refuel the crane

[GOAL5]
Use the crane to unblock the path

[GOAL5A]
Find the crusher machine

[GOAL6]
Hunt down the five hunters to open the ~blue~gate

[GOAL7]
Use the crane to unblock the path

[GOAL8]
Find the double doors to get to the exit

[GOAL9]
Find a way to the hut

[BLOCK1]
Cover the fuckin exits! Now!

[BLOCK2]
Don't let him outta here! Move it, move it!

[FUSE1]
What the - ? How many god damned times can a fuse blow?!

[FUSE2]
Aw that's just frickin' great - the fuse has fried again!

[SKN1A1]
These Skinz are boring me - dumb-assed supremacist bastards.

[SKN1A2]
Always blaming others for their inadequacies.

[SKN1A3]
Butcher them, Cash. Cut'em up, beat 'em down and choke the fucking life out of them!

[SKN2A1]
Oh, man, that one was good! The gate's open.

[SKN2A2]
Go on, get out of here!

[SKN3A1]
This shit seems content to watch porn and avoid all the action! If he won't switch it off himself,

[SKN3A2]
we'll have to do it for him!

[SKN4A1]
A crane. Well what d'ya reckon, Cash?

[SKN5A1]
Alright Cash, Grab the blade you're gonna need it to get out of here.

[SKN6A1]
You'll need to find a way through the next gate.

[SKN7A1]
Find a way to get that fat bastard out into the open!

[SKN8A1]
Excellent - Death by heavy domestic appliance!

[START]
Director : Clean the area of hunters, then make your way to the gate.

[OPEN]
Director : Nice going Cash!, The door is open.

[GASO]
Director : A busted up crane, could have some use, if you could get it working.

[DONE]
Director : Nice going Cash, scout out the area, the gates open.

[DELAY]
Hunter : That fucking fuse again, do I look like an electrician.

[HUT]
Director : You need to find a way past this gate, Cash.

[HUT1]
Director : If you could lure this fat fucker out somehow...

[ENTRY]
Hunter : Block all the exits, the only way outta here is in a body bag.

[GETTH]
Hunter : Hey you! Get the fuck outta that crane.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!