[LOCK]
{Old rusty locks like this can be broken with a well placed bullet.}
Lucchetti vecchi e arrugginiti come questo si possono far saltare con un proiettile ben assestato.

[GOAL1]
{Restore power to the rails so that the last train can leave the station}
Ripristina la corrente sui binari, in modo che l'ultimo treno possa lasciare la stazione.

[GOAL2]
{Get onto the last train before the police order its departure}
Sali sull'ultimo treno prima che la polizia lo faccia partire.

[GOAL3]
{Find a way out of this subway station}
Trova una via d'uscita dalla stazione della metropolitana.

[OHFK1]
{Oh shit, it's him!}
Oh, merda, è lui!

[OHFK2]
{Fuck, there he is!}
Cazzo, eccolo!

[OHFK3]
{It's him!}
È lui!

[LOC1]
{We are under fire! Secure the station - repeat - secure the station !!}
Siamo sotto tiro! Difendete la stazione! Ripeto! Difendete la stazione!!!

[LOC2]
{Roger - we are at the station.}
Ricevuto. Siamo alla stazione.

[LOC3]
{This is Adam11 - we've located the suspect! Send in reinforcements, now!}
Qui Adam 11, abbiamo localizzato il sospetto! Inviate rinforzi, subito!

[CHAT4]
{Do you reckon he is gonna show up?}
Credi che potrebbe farsi vivo da un momento all'altro?

[CHAT5]
{If he's got any sense he'll be long gone by now.}
Se ha un minimo di cervello, ora sarà già lontano.

[CHAT6]
{He could be watching us right now, for all we know...}
Ma potrebbe anche starci spiando, per quanto ne sappiamo...

[DISP3]
{This is dispatch to Adam11 - we have a code1 - suspect is presumed to be heading your way.}
Qui centrale a Adam 11. Abbiamo un codice 1... Si presume che il sospetto si stia dirigendo dalla vostra parte.

[SEAL1]
{Officers down! We need to seal this place right now!}
Agenti a terra! Dobbiamo isolare subito la zona!

[CHAT1]
{Seems a pretty big operation - this guy must be real dangerous!}
Sembra un'operazione di una certa portata... Pare che l'uomo sia pericoloso!

[CHAT2]
{I don't like this, they only pull out all the stops for real nut jobs!}
Si direbbe qualcosa di serio... altrimenti non si spiegherebbe un simile sbarramento.

[CHAT3]
{He must be a terrorist or something - they ain't leaving nothing to chance!}
Dev'essere un terrorista o qualcosa del genere... Non lasciano niente al caso!

[SWAT1]
{This is Bravo leader, regroup at the tracks!}
Qui capo Bravo, raggruppatevi ai binari!

[SWAT2]
{Roger Alpha team, Charlie is en route from the precinct as we speak.}
Ricevuto, squadra Alfa. Charlie operativo. Abbiamo appena lasciato il distretto.

[SWAT3]
{This is Charlie leader. Power has been shut off. Repeat - power is off!}
Qui capo Charlie. La corrente è stata staccata. Ripeto... corrente staccata!

[MID1A1]
{<radio static> sure you will never get out of that subway alive <radio static>}
<ronzio> di sicuro non uscirai vivo da quella metropolitana <ronzio>

[DIR1]
Director: <static>...sure you'll never get out of that subway alive, Cash...<static>

[START1]
Roger Dispatch - we are in.

[DIA1_3]
Shit! It's him!

[2_1RGT]
This is Bravo Leader - regroup at the tracks!

[2_1ZI]
THIS IS BRAVO LEADER, TARGET SIGHTED! ZERO IN MY POSITION!

[2_2ZI]
THIS IS BRAVO 2, TARGET SIGHTED! REPEAT - TARGET SIGHTED!

[2_3ZI]
THIS IS BRAVO 3, I HAVE SIGHT OF THE TARGET

[COPS1]
Do you reckon he is gonna show up here?

[COPS2]
Dont know, but they are sending cops at all terminals...hope we dont meet the guy.

[RADIO1]
We are under fire! Secure the station - repeat - secure the station!

[RADIO2]
Officer down! Bravo 1 please respond - seal the perimeter right now!

[RADIO3]
Roger TEAM1, Bravo team is moving in to your position

[RADIO4]
This is Charlie Leader. Power to the rails has been disconnected. Repeat - POWER IS OFF

[RADIO5]
This is Adam 11 - We have the fugitive! Send in reinforcements!!

[RADIO6]
This is dispatch - we have a code 11 - Fugitive is presumed to be heading your way

[RADIO7]
We have a situation - Fugitive has reconnected power to the rails - repeat POWER IS ON.

[RADIO8]
Move that fucking train out of there!!

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!