[GOAL1]
Restore power to the rails so that the last train can leave the station

[GOAL2]
Get onto the last train before the police order its departure

[GOAL3]
Find a way out of this subway station

[LOCK]
Old rusty locks like this can be broken with a well placed bullet.

[OHFK1]
Oh shit, it's him!

[OHFK2]
Fuck, there he is!

[OHFK3]
It's him!

[LOC1]
We are under fire! Secure the station - repeat - secure the station !!

[LOC2]
Roger - we are at the station.

[LOC3]
This is Adam11 - we've located the suspect! Send in reinforcements, now!

[CHAT4]
Do you reckon he is gonna show up?

[CHAT5]
If he's got any sense he'll be long gone by now.

[CHAT6]
He could be watching us right now, for all we know...

[DISP3]
This is dispatch to Adam11 - we have a code1 - suspect is presumed to be heading your way.

[SEAL1]
Officers down! We need to seal this place right now!

[CHAT1]
Seems a pretty big operation - this guy must be real dangerous!

[CHAT2]
I don't like this, they only pull out all the stops for real nut jobs!

[CHAT3]
He must be a terrorist or something - they ain't leaving nothing to chance!

[SWAT1]
This is Bravo leader, regroup at the tracks!

[SWAT2]
Roger Alpha team, Charlie is en route from the precinct as we speak.

[SWAT3]
This is Charlie leader. Power has been shut off. Repeat - power is off!

[MID1A1]
<radio static> sure you will never get out of that subway alive <radio static>

[DIR1]
Director: <static>...sure you'll never get out of that subway alive, Cash...<static>

[START1]
Roger Dispatch - we are in.

[DIA1_3]
Shit! It's him!

[2_1RGT]
This is Bravo Leader - regroup at the tracks!

[2_1ZI]
THIS IS BRAVO LEADER, TARGET SIGHTED! ZERO IN MY POSITION!

[2_2ZI]
THIS IS BRAVO 2, TARGET SIGHTED! REPEAT - TARGET SIGHTED!

[2_3ZI]
THIS IS BRAVO 3, I HAVE SIGHT OF THE TARGET

[COPS1]
Do you reckon he is gonna show up here?

[COPS2]
Dont know, but they are sending cops at all terminals...hope we dont meet the guy.

[RADIO1]
We are under fire! Secure the station - repeat - secure the station!

[RADIO2]
Officer down! Bravo 1 please respond - seal the perimeter right now!

[RADIO3]
Roger TEAM1, Bravo team is moving in to your position

[RADIO4]
This is Charlie Leader. Power to the rails has been disconnected. Repeat - POWER IS OFF

[RADIO5]
This is Adam 11 - We have the fugitive! Send in reinforcements!!

[RADIO6]
This is dispatch - we have a code 11 - Fugitive is presumed to be heading your way

[RADIO7]
We have a situation - Fugitive has reconnected power to the rails - repeat POWER IS ON.

[RADIO8]
Move that fucking train out of there!!

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!