[LOCK]
{Old rusty locks like this can be broken with a well placed bullet.}
Las cerraduras viejas y oxidadas, como ésta, pueden romperse con un buen balazo

[GOAL1]
{Restore power to the rails so that the last train can leave the station}
Haz que los raíles vuelvan a tener energía para que el último tren pueda salir de la estación

[GOAL2]
{Get onto the last train before the police order its departure}
Entra en el último tren antes de que la policía ordene su partida

[GOAL3]
{Find a way out of this subway station}
Encuentra una forma de salir de la estación de metro

[OHFK1]
{Oh shit, it's him!}
¡Mierda! ¡Es él!

[OHFK2]
{Fuck, there he is!}
¡Joder, ahí está!

[OHFK3]
{It's him!}
¡Es él!

[LOC1]
{We are under fire! Secure the station - repeat - secure the station !!}
¡Nos están disparando! ¡¡Asegurad la estación!! Repito, ¡¡asegurad la estación!!

[LOC2]
{Roger - we are at the station.}
Entendido, estamos en la estación.

[LOC3]
{This is Adam11 - we've located the suspect! Send in reinforcements, now!}
Aquí Adam11, ¡hemos localizado al sospechoso! Enviad refuerzos, ¡ya!

[CHAT4]
{Do you reckon he is gonna show up?}
¿Crees que va a dar la cara?

[CHAT5]
{If he's got any sense he'll be long gone by now.}
Si tiene un poco de sentido común, ahora mismo estará muy lejos.

[CHAT6]
{He could be watching us right now, for all we know...}
Por lo que sabemos, podría estar vigilándonos ahora mismo...

[DISP3]
{This is dispatch to Adam11 - we have a code1 - suspect is presumed to be heading your way.}
Central a Adam11, tenemos un código 1, se cree que el sospechoso se dirige hacia allí

[SEAL1]
{Officers down! We need to seal this place right now!}
¡Oficiales caídos! ¡Tenemos que aislar este lugar, inmediatamente!

[CHAT1]
{Seems a pretty big operation - this guy must be real dangerous!}
Parece una operación bastante grande, ¡este tío tiene que ser peligroso de verdad!

[CHAT2]
{I don't like this, they only pull out all the stops for real nut jobs!}
No me gusta, parece serio... ¡de otro modo no se explicaría tal bloqueo!

[CHAT3]
{He must be a terrorist or something - they ain't leaving nothing to chance!}
Tiene que ser un terrorista o algo así, ¡no están dejando nada al azar!

[SWAT1]
{This is Bravo leader, regroup at the tracks!}
Aquí líder Bravo, ¡reagrupaos en los caminos!

[SWAT2]
{Roger Alpha team, Charlie is en route from the precinct as we speak.}
Oído, equipo Alfa, mientras hablamos, Charlie va de camino.

[SWAT3]
{This is Charlie leader. Power has been shut off. Repeat - power is off!}
Aquí líder Charlie. La energía ha sido cortada. Repito, ¡la energía ha sido cortada!

[MID1A1]
{<radio static> sure you will never get out of that subway alive <radio static>}
<estática> seguro que no saldrás vivo del metro <estática>

[DIR1]
Director: <static>...sure you'll never get out of that subway alive, Cash...<static>

[START1]
Roger Dispatch - we are in.

[DIA1_3]
Shit! It's him!

[2_1RGT]
This is Bravo Leader - regroup at the tracks!

[2_1ZI]
THIS IS BRAVO LEADER, TARGET SIGHTED! ZERO IN MY POSITION!

[2_2ZI]
THIS IS BRAVO 2, TARGET SIGHTED! REPEAT - TARGET SIGHTED!

[2_3ZI]
THIS IS BRAVO 3, I HAVE SIGHT OF THE TARGET

[COPS1]
Do you reckon he is gonna show up here?

[COPS2]
Dont know, but they are sending cops at all terminals...hope we dont meet the guy.

[RADIO1]
We are under fire! Secure the station - repeat - secure the station!

[RADIO2]
Officer down! Bravo 1 please respond - seal the perimeter right now!

[RADIO3]
Roger TEAM1, Bravo team is moving in to your position

[RADIO4]
This is Charlie Leader. Power to the rails has been disconnected. Repeat - POWER IS OFF

[RADIO5]
This is Adam 11 - We have the fugitive! Send in reinforcements!!

[RADIO6]
This is dispatch - we have a code 11 - Fugitive is presumed to be heading your way

[RADIO7]
We have a situation - Fugitive has reconnected power to the rails - repeat POWER IS ON.

[RADIO8]
Move that fucking train out of there!!

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!