[GOAL1]
{Make your way to the end of the Trainyard}
Arriva in fondo al deposito dei treni.

[DISP4]
{The suspect is believed to be in the area, approach with extreme caution!}
Si suppone che il sospetto sia in zona, avvicinarsi con la massima cautela!

[DISP5]
{He is armed and is considered to be highly dangerous!}
È armato e si suppone anche molto pericoloso!

[FREEZ1]
{Freeze Punk! Just give me an excuse to waste you.}
Fermati bastardo! Non cerco che una scusa per eliminarti.

[FREEZ2]
{CCPD! Hold it right there!}
Polizia! Fermo dove sei!

[FREEZ3]
{Not another inch, asshole!}
Non un altro passo, pezzo di merda!

[CAPT1]
{Be advised, Dispatch, we have the animal!}
Centrale, l'animale è nelle nostre mani!

[CAPT2]
{Dispatch! Dispatch! We got the bastard!}
Centrale! Centrale! Abbiamo trovato il bastardo!

[CAPT3]
{Fuckin'A - We got him! Woohoo!}
Ci siamo... è nostro! Woohoo!

[MPG1]
{Put your fucking hands up!}
Alza quelle fottute mani!

[MPG2]
{Shoot that copkiller sonofabitch!}
Uccidete quel figlio di puttana ammazza poliziotti!

[MPG3]
{What the fuck is this?}
Cosa diavolo sta succedendo?

[MPG4]
{Shoot that cop killin sonofabitch!}
Uccidete quel fottuto elimina-poliziotti!

[GAMEGOD]
{To jump from wagon to wagon and over big gaps, run as fast as you can towards the edge and the player will jump automatically.}
Per saltare da un vagone all'altro e superare ampi spazi, corri più veloce che puoi fino al bordo e spiccherai automaticamente un balzo.

[INTRO]
COP : JUST KEEP YOUR EYES PEELED HES AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE, WEVE GOT THE ACCESS TO THE TRACK LOCKED

[SNIPER]
COP : AND SWAT HAVE A SNIPER IN THE WATER TOWER WITH A GOOD VIEW OF THE TRACK SO HE AINT GOING NOWHERE WITHOUT US KNOWING

[DEAD]
COP : WE GOT HIM HE AINT GONNA BE CAUSING US ANYMORE TROUBLE

[RADIO1]
POLICE RADIO: The suspect is believed to be in the area, approach with extreme caution .

[RADIO2]
POLICE RADIO: He is armed and considered dangerous.

[CAPTUR1]
COP: Freeze Fucker! Just give me an excuse to waste you.

[CAPTUR2]
COP ON RADIO: Control we have captured the suspect.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!