[GOAL1]
{Make your way to the end of the Trainyard}
Traverse le dépôt ferroviaire.

[DISP4]
{The suspect is believed to be in the area, approach with extreme caution!}
Le suspect se trouverait dans le secteur, soyez très prudents.

[DISP5]
{He is armed and is considered to be highly dangerous!}
Il est armé et extrêmement dangereux !

[FREEZ1]
{Freeze Punk! Just give me an excuse to waste you.}
Bouge plus ! Allez, donne-moi une raison de te buter !

[FREEZ2]
{CCPD! Hold it right there!}
Police ! On ne bouge plus !

[FREEZ3]
{Not another inch, asshole!}
Bouge pas d'un sourcil, connard !

[CAPT1]
{Be advised, Dispatch, we have the animal!}
Central, on a le psycho !

[CAPT2]
{Dispatch! Dispatch! We got the bastard!}
Central ! Central ! On a eu le salopard !

[CAPT3]
{Fuckin'A - We got him! Woohoo!}
Putain de merde, on l'a eu !

[MPG1]
{Put your fucking hands up!}
Les mains sur la tête !

[MPG2]
{Shoot that copkiller sonofabitch!}
Bute cet enfoiré de tueur de flics !

[MPG3]
{What the fuck is this?}
C'est quoi cette merde ?

[MPG4]
{Shoot that cop killin sonofabitch!}
Bute ce salud de flic de mes deux !

[GAMEGOD]
{To jump from wagon to wagon and over big gaps, run as fast as you can towards the edge and the player will jump automatically.}
Pour passer de wagon en wagon ou franchir des trous, cours très vite jusqu'au bord et tu sauteras automatiquement.

[INTRO]
COP : JUST KEEP YOUR EYES PEELED HES AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE, WEVE GOT THE ACCESS TO THE TRACK LOCKED

[SNIPER]
COP : AND SWAT HAVE A SNIPER IN THE WATER TOWER WITH A GOOD VIEW OF THE TRACK SO HE AINT GOING NOWHERE WITHOUT US KNOWING

[DEAD]
COP : WE GOT HIM HE AINT GONNA BE CAUSING US ANYMORE TROUBLE

[RADIO1]
POLICE RADIO: The suspect is believed to be in the area, approach with extreme caution .

[RADIO2]
POLICE RADIO: He is armed and considered dangerous.

[CAPTUR1]
COP: Freeze Fucker! Just give me an excuse to waste you.

[CAPTUR2]
COP ON RADIO: Control we have captured the suspect.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!