[GOAL1]
{Make your way to the end of the Trainyard}
Ábrete camino hasta el final de la estación.

[DISP4]
{The suspect is believed to be in the area, approach with extreme caution!}
Se cree que el sospechoso está en la zona, ¡acérquense con toda la precaución posible!

[DISP5]
{He is armed and is considered to be highly dangerous!}
¡Está armado y se le considera muy peligroso!

[FREEZ1]
{Freeze Punk! Just give me an excuse to waste you.}
¡Quieto, capullo! Dame una excusa para acabar contigo.

[FREEZ2]
{CCPD! Hold it right there!}
¡Policía de Carcer City! ¡Quieto, no se mueva!

[FREEZ3]
{Not another inch, asshole!}
¡Ni un paso más, gilipollas!

[CAPT1]
{Be advised, Dispatch, we have the animal!}
Central, ¡tenemos al animal!

[CAPT2]
{Dispatch! Dispatch! We got the bastard!}
¡Central! ¡Central! ¡Tenemos al bastardo!

[CAPT3]
{Fuckin'A - We got him! Woohoo!}
Coño, ¡le tenemos! ¡Yuuujuuuu!

[MPG1]
{Put your fucking hands up!}
¡Levanta las putas manos!

[MPG2]
{Shoot that copkiller sonofabitch!}
¡Disparad al hijo puta asesino de policías!

[MPG3]
{What the fuck is this?}
¿Qué coño es esto?

[MPG4]
{Shoot that cop killin sonofabitch!}
¡Dispara a ese cabrón asesino de policías!

[GAMEGOD]
{To jump from wagon to wagon and over big gaps, run as fast as you can towards the edge and the player will jump automatically.}
Para saltar de vagón a vagón y sobre grandes espacios, corre todo lo que puedas hacia el borde y el jugador saltará automáticamente.

[INTRO]
COP : JUST KEEP YOUR EYES PEELED HES AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE, WEVE GOT THE ACCESS TO THE TRACK LOCKED

[SNIPER]
COP : AND SWAT HAVE A SNIPER IN THE WATER TOWER WITH A GOOD VIEW OF THE TRACK SO HE AINT GOING NOWHERE WITHOUT US KNOWING

[DEAD]
COP : WE GOT HIM HE AINT GONNA BE CAUSING US ANYMORE TROUBLE

[RADIO1]
POLICE RADIO: The suspect is believed to be in the area, approach with extreme caution .

[RADIO2]
POLICE RADIO: He is armed and considered dangerous.

[CAPTUR1]
COP: Freeze Fucker! Just give me an excuse to waste you.

[CAPTUR2]
COP ON RADIO: Control we have captured the suspect.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!