[GOAL1]
{Make your way to the end of the Trainyard}
Begib dich ans Ende des Bahnhofgeländes.

[DISP4]
{The suspect is believed to be in the area, approach with extreme caution!}
Der Verdächtige wird in diesem Bereich vermutet. Annäherung nur mit extremer Vorsicht!

[DISP5]
{He is armed and is considered to be highly dangerous!}
Er ist bewaffnet und äußerst gefährlich!

[FREEZ1]
{Freeze Punk! Just give me an excuse to waste you.}
Keine Bewegung, Penner! Gib mir nur einen Grund, und ich mach dich alle.

[FREEZ2]
{CCPD! Hold it right there!}
CCPD! Sofort stehenbleiben!

[FREEZ3]
{Not another inch, asshole!}
Keinen Schritt weiter, Arschloch!

[CAPT1]
{Be advised, Dispatch, we have the animal!}
Nachricht an Zentrale, wir haben die Missgeburt!

[CAPT2]
{Dispatch! Dispatch! We got the bastard!}
Zentrale! Zentrale! Wir haben den Bastard!

[CAPT3]
{Fuckin'A - We got him! Woohoo!}
Scheiße noch mal - Wir haben ihn! Jaaaa!

[MPG1]
{Put your fucking hands up!}
Nimm deine dreckigen Hände hoch!

[MPG2]
{Shoot that copkiller sonofabitch!}
Erschießt diesen Scheißkerl von Cop-Killer!

[MPG3]
{What the fuck is this?}
Was zum Teufel ist das?

[MPG4]
{Shoot that cop killin sonofabitch!}
Erschießt diesen verschissenen Cop-Killer!

[GAMEGOD]
{To jump from wagon to wagon and over big gaps, run as fast as you can towards the edge and the player will jump automatically.}
Um von Waggon zu Waggon und über weite Lücken zu springen, musst du so schnell du kannst auf den Rand zulaufen, dann springt die Spielfigur automatisch.

[INTRO]
COP : JUST KEEP YOUR EYES PEELED HES AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE, WEVE GOT THE ACCESS TO THE TRACK LOCKED

[SNIPER]
COP : AND SWAT HAVE A SNIPER IN THE WATER TOWER WITH A GOOD VIEW OF THE TRACK SO HE AINT GOING NOWHERE WITHOUT US KNOWING

[DEAD]
COP : WE GOT HIM HE AINT GONNA BE CAUSING US ANYMORE TROUBLE

[RADIO1]
POLICE RADIO: The suspect is believed to be in the area, approach with extreme caution .

[RADIO2]
POLICE RADIO: He is armed and considered dangerous.

[CAPTUR1]
COP: Freeze Fucker! Just give me an excuse to waste you.

[CAPTUR2]
COP ON RADIO: Control we have captured the suspect.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!