[INTRO]
COP : JUST KEEP YOUR EYES PEELED HES AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE, WEVE GOT THE ACCESS TO THE TRACK LOCKED

[SNIPER]
COP : AND SWAT HAVE A SNIPER IN THE WATER TOWER WITH A GOOD VIEW OF THE TRACK SO HE AINT GOING NOWHERE WITHOUT US KNOWING

[DEAD]
COP : WE GOT HIM HE AINT GONNA BE CAUSING US ANYMORE TROUBLE

[RADIO1]
POLICE RADIO: The suspect is believed to be in the area, approach with extreme caution .

[RADIO2]
POLICE RADIO: He is armed and considered dangerous.

[CAPTUR1]
COP: Freeze Fucker! Just give me an excuse to waste you.

[CAPTUR2]
COP ON RADIO: Control we have captured the suspect.

[GOAL1]
Make your way to the end of the Trainyard

[DISP4]
The suspect is believed to be in the area, approach with extreme caution!

[DISP5]
He is armed and is considered to be highly dangerous!

[FREEZ1]
Freeze Punk! Just give me an excuse to waste you.

[FREEZ2]
CCPD! Hold it right there!

[FREEZ3]
Not another inch, asshole!

[CAPT1]
Be advised, Dispatch, we have the animal!

[CAPT2]
Dispatch! Dispatch! We got the bastard!

[CAPT3]
Fuckin'A - We got him! Woohoo!

[MPG1]
Put your fucking hands up!

[MPG2]
Shoot that copkiller sonofabitch!

[MPG3]
What the fuck is this?

[MPG4]
Shoot that cop killin sonofabitch!

[GAMEGOD]
To jump from wagon to wagon and over big gaps, run as fast as you can towards the edge and the player will jump automatically.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!