[SHOT]
{You've been tranquilized, while in this state you won't be able to use the crowbar, wait until the effects have worn off.}
Du wurdest betäubt. In diesem Zustand kannst du die Brechstange nicht benutzen. Warte, bis die Wirkung nachlässt.

[RIFLE]
{Hold down the Action2 button to use the scope. You can zoom in and out using the movement buttons on the keyboard.}
Halte die Aktionstaste2 gedrückt, um den Zoom zu aktivieren. Mit den Bewegungstasten auf der Tastatur kannst du heran- und wegzoomen.

[GOAL1]
{Find a weapon and get past the ~blue~rope-tied ~colour~door}
Finde eine Waffe und überwinde die Tür, die mit einem ~blue~Tau zugebunden ~colour~ist.

[GOAL2]
{Get past the ~blue~padlocked ~colour~gate}
Du musst durch das Tor mit dem ~blue~Vorhängeschloss ~colour~gelangen.

[GOAL3]
{Find a way into the ~blue~restaurant ~colour~at the top of the zoo}
Such dir einen Weg oben in das ~blue~Restaurant ~colour~im Zoo.

[GOAL4]
{Go out the back of the restaurant to the ~blue~exit}
Verlasse das Restaurant durch die Hintertür und gehe zum ~blue~Ausgang.

[GOAL5]
{Make your way to the zoo pens}
Schlage dich zu den Zoo-Gehegen durch.

[SOU1A1]
{These pricks call themselves the Wardogs - real dickless gung-ho losers}
Und diese Wichser schimpfen sich Wardogs - diese Versager

[SOU1A2]
{You're gonna have to tool up if you're gonna make it - take it slow and see what you can take from these guys.}
Du musst dir unbedingt Waffen besorgen - geh es langsam an und sieh mal, ob du diesen Typen ein paar Waffen abnehmen kannst.

[SOU2A1]
{There are some doors over the otherside of this location that will get your sorry hide out of here.}
Auf der anderen Seite dieses Drehortes sind ein paar Türen, durch die du hier verschwinden kannst.

[SOU3A1]
{Where did I hide that crowbar? Think, think, think!}
Wo habe ich nur die Brechstange versteckt? Denk nach, denk nach!

[SOU3A2]
{Sorry Cash, this is a grizzly situation...}
Tut mir Leid, Cash, aber hier steppt der Bär ...

[SOU4A1]
{Oh hell, that wasn't in the script! Honest Cash, they're making it up as they're going along, I swear!}
Verdammt, das stand nicht im Drehbuch! Ehrlich, Cash, die lassen sich das spontan einfallen, ich schwör's dir!

[MPG1]
{Give him the fucking food, enough bullshitting.}
Gib ihm das beschissene Essen, du hast genug rumgealbert.

[MPG2]
{Give him the fucking food!}
Gib ihm das verschissene Essen!

[MPG3]
{Ah fuck! This guy fucking stinks!}
Oh Scheiße! Der Kerl stinkt vielleicht!

[MPG4]
{Just give him the fucking food and let's get the hell out of here.}
Gib ihm einfach das verdammte Essen und dann nichts wie weg hier.

[MPG5]
{Fall in and listen up!}
Antreten und zuhören!

[MPG6]
{At ease. It's time to get out there and nail that bastard!}
Rührt euch. Es ist an der Zeit da raus zu gehen und diesen Bastard umzunieten!

[MPG7]
{WARDOGS - YEEAH!}
WARDOGS - JAAAAAAA!

[MPG8]
{Ha Ha!}
Ha ha!

[OLD1]
{Jesus Christ! Come on, give this stinking guy his food.}
Scheiße! Komm schon, gib dem Mistkerl sein Essen.

[OLD2]
{This ain't time for games.}
Jetzt ist keine Zeit für Spielchen.

[OLD3]
{Alright!}
In Ordnung!

[OLD4]
{Just give it to him.}
Gib's ihm einfach.

[INTRO]
{Director : These pricks will kill you in a second if you're unarmed. Find an Executor and steal his weapon.}
Director : These pricks will kill you in a second unarmed, find an executor, and steal his weapon.

[PAD1]
Director : Where could that crowbar be, maybe the bear took it.

[TOP]
Director : Lets see if you can figure this one out. Be careful Cash, some of these wardogs have tranquilizer rifles.

[PAD]
Director : Find these doors and get past them, you'll need to find a crowbar first!!

[CHECK1]
{Kill the two hunters to open this door.}
Director : Kill those two pricks first, then I'll open this door.

[CHECK2]
{Kill the last hunter to open this door.}
Director : Find and kill the last hunter and I'll open the door.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!