[SHOT]
{You've been tranquilized, while in this state you won't be able to use the crowbar, wait until the effects have worn off.}
Sei stato narcotizzato e non sei in grado di utilizzare il piede di porco. Aspetta che passi l'effetto dei tranquillanti.

[RIFLE]
{Hold down the Action2 button to use the scope. You can zoom in and out using the movement buttons on the keyboard.}
Tieni premuto il tasto Azione2 per regolare l'obiettivo. Puoi zoomare avanti e indietro usando i tasti freccia della tastiera.

[GOAL1]
{Find a weapon and get past the ~blue~rope-tied ~colour~door}
Trova un'arma e supera il ~blue~cancello~colour~.

[GOAL2]
{Get past the ~blue~padlocked ~colour~gate}
Supera il cancello chiuso con il ~blue~lucchetto~colour~.

[GOAL3]
{Find a way into the ~blue~restaurant ~colour~at the top of the zoo}
Trova il modo di raggiungere il ~blue~ristorante ~colour~sopra lo zoo.

[GOAL4]
{Go out the back of the restaurant to the ~blue~exit}
Raggiungi l'~blue~uscita ~colour~sul retro del ristorante.

[GOAL5]
{Make your way to the zoo pens}
Raggiungi i recinti degli animali.

[SOU1A1]
{These pricks call themselves the Wardogs - real dickless gung-ho losers}
Questi stronzi si fanno chiamare Wardogs... dei veri perdenti senza coglioni...

[SOU1A2]
{You're gonna have to tool up if you're gonna make it - take it slow and see what you can take from these guys.}
Dovrai ingegnarti non poco per venirne fuori... ma credo che i tuoi nuovi amici riusciranno in qualche modo ad aiutarti...

[SOU2A1]
{There are some doors over the otherside of this location that will get your sorry hide out of here.}
Ci sono delle porte all'altra estremità del set che ti permetteranno di togliere il disturbo.

[SOU3A1]
{Where did I hide that crowbar? Think, think, think!}
Dove ho nascosto quel piede di porco? Vediamo un po'...

[SOU3A2]
{Sorry Cash, this is a grizzly situation...}
Mi spiace Cash, è una brutta situazione...

[SOU4A1]
{Oh hell, that wasn't in the script! Honest Cash, they're making it up as they're going along, I swear!}
Dannazione, questo non era previsto! Davvero Cash, ti giuro che il copione era completamento diverso!

[MPG1]
{Give him the fucking food, enough bullshitting.}
Dagli il suo fottuto cibo e andiamocene al più presto da qui.

[MPG2]
{Give him the fucking food!}
Dagli il suo fottuto cibo!

[MPG3]
{Ah fuck! This guy fucking stinks!}
Che schifo! C'è un fetore che ti brucia le narici.

[MPG4]
{Just give him the fucking food and let's get the hell out of here.}
Diamogli da mangiare e andiamocene subito da questa fogna.

[MPG5]
{Fall in and listen up!}
Mettetevi in riga e ascoltatemi!

[MPG6]
{At ease. It's time to get out there and nail that bastard!}
Riposo. È ora di uscire di qui e inchiodare quel bastardo!

[MPG7]
{WARDOGS - YEEAH!}
WARDOGS... YEEAH!

[MPG8]
{Ha Ha!}
Ah ah!

[OLD1]
{Jesus Christ! Come on, give this stinking guy his food.}
Insomma! Muoviti, dai da mangiare a questo puzzone.

[OLD2]
{This ain't time for games.}
Non è il momento di giocare.

[OLD3]
{Alright!}
Va bene!

[OLD4]
{Just give it to him.}
Daglielo e basta.

[INTRO]
{Director : These pricks will kill you in a second if you're unarmed. Find an Executor and steal his weapon.}
Director : These pricks will kill you in a second unarmed, find an executor, and steal his weapon.

[PAD1]
Director : Where could that crowbar be, maybe the bear took it.

[TOP]
Director : Lets see if you can figure this one out. Be careful Cash, some of these wardogs have tranquilizer rifles.

[PAD]
Director : Find these doors and get past them, you'll need to find a crowbar first!!

[CHECK1]
{Kill the two hunters to open this door.}
Director : Kill those two pricks first, then I'll open this door.

[CHECK2]
{Kill the last hunter to open this door.}
Director : Find and kill the last hunter and I'll open the door.

[DUMMY]
THIS LABEL NEEDS TO BE HERE !!!
AS THE LAST LABEL DOES NOT GET COMPILED!!